Dang it!
How could you tell?
I can't blend yet!
No!
You got me!
I was trying to be stealthy with that one.
What's up people?
I realized I forgot a timer.
But I usually just come back around... well six or whatever the time is set for the stream.
I usually do all kinds of things.
So I guess it was fine.
By the way, check out the work I did on the on the jamming mode.
The background has been removed.
But for some reason it doesn't appear to be removed from the stream itself.
That's weird.
That's odd.
Or am I crazy?
Yeah, background is definitely removed on that.
Oliver, you have to set up the 7TV modes to show on screen.
Oh, I thought I already did that!
I went into... hold on.
So I'm on the 7TV page now.
And it says about Oliver's emotes.
I added 40 emotes.
And I assigned them to Twitch channel Oliver.
And I clicked save changes.
It should work.
Did you do it in stream labs?
Oh, I don't use stream labs.
I use stream elements.
Do I have to do it there?
Wait, does it work in the chat here?
Or does it just not work in the preview on this stream?
Because what you're seeing on stream is through stream elements.
What you're seeing on your own screen in the chat is of course whatever you have installed.
We see it in the chat but not on video.
Ah, okay.
Then it has to be stream elements.
I don't know how to do that, guys.
How do I change that?
I mean, I guess you don't know that.
Let me see your chat.
Streaming tools.
Let me go to the settings of the chat.
The chat overlay.
Okay, settings.
There's there's no real... there's nothing that suggests any kind of option for 7 TV at all.
Perhaps the stream elements has a cache and it's using it instead of the current one.
That's that's a possibility.
I could try and... hold on.
Let me try and reload it.
Maybe 7 TV and all that is already built in by default.
I don't know how to reload it though.
Hold on.
Switch chat.
Oh wait, I think I know how.
I'm gonna Did you know that it's one year anniversary of your starting the Minecraft series?
I did not know that.
Is that today?
Holy shit, it's already been a year.
That's crazy.
Boy, are we getting old.
That's nuts.
Yeah, it still doesn't work, it seems.
I don't know what to do.
That there's no setting for 7 TV that I can find.
Nothing like that.
Hmm, that's odd.
Okay, I'll try and figure it out for next time, I guess.
That's unfortunate.
I'm sorry, I tried to fix it for today.
Maybe I need the... no, I don't think I need to have the 7 TV installed because that's just for me locally to see it in my chat, right?
Like I'm logged into 7 TV and I linked to my channel and I added the emotes.
I did all of that.
So obviously it works for you guys, it just doesn't work through stream elements.
So there's something going on there.
Isanti and Dagbo.
Thanks for resubscribing and subscribing.
I appreciate it guys.
And TigerJoe for following, thank you very much.
Okay, so has the to-do list been updated in a while?
Actually it has, I'll show you.
Let me zoom over a bit here.
So I updated the list to remove some of the stuff I already did and added some new stuff.
There's still plenty of stuff I haven't added yet just because I didn't think of it at the time, but I'm gonna add it as I go.
Obviously we gotta murder the boss in the ancient laboratory.
Triangle thing in the art?
Something about an egg?
By the way, I watched the intro cinematic again just for that.
And then I have to experiment with the music wand somehow.
Maybe it's related to the note we found in the magical temple or it's somehow related to the music boxes around the world, you know?
Who knows?
We gotta do some stuff there.
So that's on the to-do list and of course to fill out this map as much as we can.
Speaking of, I was watching this segment again of last VOD.
This right here.
And it occurred to me it's not actually embedded in the wall like that.
There's a little bit of an outcrop so I have to change that.
Other than that, I figured out something awesome thanks to you guys on the discord.
So I think I fixed the crashing forever now.
I was using a third-party app called Special K to allow me to run the game in the background when I all tapped.
Such that the transition would be more smooth when going from the drawing software to the game.
But it turns out there's an option for that in the game to do it.
Somewhere.
There.
Pause the game when unfocused.
Why is it hidden in the input?
Put it in general or graphics.
It's so weird.
Yeah.
So hopefully no more crashing.
I was so nervous last time.
That's why I didn't open the overlay that much.
After that incident I was scared of switching the scene in fear of the whole game crashing and ruining my save.
That's why I started drawing at the very end last time after I clicked save and exit.
I feel so much better about this now.
Okay, so that's fixed.
That's awesome.
Guys, I'm in the middle of a run and things are going pretty well.
I'm not gonna, you know, I'm not gonna jinx anything here.
It's not a jinx.
This is not a jinx.
I'm just saying it's going really well.
And I want to continue that.
So I'm gonna jump right in guys and have some fun here.
I'm also gonna turn off this cave music.
Contemplation cave.
There we go.
Okay, I'm so ready.
Today we're drinking water.
And the reason is I was at the dentist today and the dentist told me, well didn't tell me that there was something wrong, but basically was like, oh you don't drink like soda, do you?
And I was like, yes.
So now I feel a little guilty.
So now I'm drinking water.
At least today.
Just to respect the work they did on my teeth.
Okay, let's go.
Oh, I'm gonna close you guys down and then I'll see you guys on the other side.
Okay.
Oh my god.
Oh, imagine if I died immediately there.
Oh lordy.
I need to remember what I did and all that stuff.
Is he dead?
He dead.
Good.
Okay, so we have... okay.
This guy is scared of the place here.
Watch.
He's not gonna come near here.
That's right, bitch.
Stay put.
Okay.
Let's just look what we got.
We have this one right here.
We have a long-distance teleport.
Then we have... I don't know why that is there.
Oh yeah, right.
I wanted to fire a black hole into here.
Oh, but then I decided not to do it because I'm scared of maybe a boss coming out.
And I'm not full HP.
Yeah, that's where I ended.
I was gonna do this and then I changed my mind because I was scared of a boss.
So I'm gonna get rid of one spell here.
Maybe... what should I get rid of?
I don't even know.
Maybe the magic bolt.
Let's put this here and then put this spell up here for now.
Let's just organize it a bit.
This one though, I'm not sure I... I'm gonna keep it for now.
I'm gonna keep it.
This one right here is sick.
It's a great wand.
It can probably be made even better with more mana and stuff, but that's gonna add some castor lay, right?
I mean, it's already pretty good.
Yeah, that's pretty good.
Wait, speed up?
Did I forget to put that bag in there?
I guess I must have forgot.
But that's good.
We want more... more speed is good.
More speed is good.
Okay, let's go heal a bit.
And I figured out a big thing, by the way.
You can put blood in a potion, of course, and drink it directly from the potion.
That changed everything.
And just to confirm, right now I am in the art, right?
I think I am.
Well, you know what, actually?
Let's just do that right now.
So don't forget.
Let me see.
It's like... there's like a little opening leading to a triangle.
Okay.
So really what it is, something like this.
The triangle can stay.
This one can get removed.
No, no, no, no.
Remove the little line.
Delete stroke.
No?
Okay.
Guess I'll make a new one.
Also, this is a bit too thick.
It opens something like that.
And then there's like a triangle.
Just sitting there menacingly.
Let me make it a bit thinner.
And there's a drawing of... you know what, actually, I'm going to make it zoom out.
I'm going to make it a bit bigger.
Like that.
Someone's moaning in the background of the game, and it makes me uncomfortable.
But it is what it is.
And then draw it to here.
Not the wrong size.
There we go.
And inside of this, there's a drawing of an egg.
Interesting, huh?
I wonder what's inside of that.
We're going to figure it out.
Okay.
Draw as we go along.
Now I'm not scared of crashing anymore.
Feels good, man.
And then I need to figure out how to use this heal on myself.
That's actually a big thing.
I really need to figure that out.
And I need to get away from this dude.
Got some blood here.
That means we can pick it up.
Oh, wait, what?
Wait, what is this?
Giga black hole?
What the fuck is that?
Yo, huh?
What?
How did I miss this shit last time?
Was I not over here?
Oh, will you please leave me alone?
What is this lightning thrower?
9,200 for that?
Holy crap.
I don't have enough money.
Whoa.
There's a wand here too.
Huh.
Energy orb with a trigger.
I kind of want more triggers.
I don't really have any triggers.
Maybe you should get one.
Just let's have a trigger.
Let's have a trigger.
That seems good.
Okay.
We got to find some gold and blood.
Speaking of blood, there's plenty of blood here.
To fill up our bottle.
It's gonna fill up with some slime though, no?
Wait, does slime even go in?
It does go in.
Okay.
What is that one?
Empty wand.
I'm so excited about this run.
And the crazy thing is, I'm also excited about the next run.
Whenever that is.
That's what this game does, man.
Just makes you excited.
All the time.
I'm safe here, right?
Get the blood.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Fill it up, fill it up, fill it up.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Oh, nice.
My shield absorbs that.
Well almost.
I'm kind of stuck here.
Drink.
Gotta find more blood.
What is happening here?
This looks mysterious to me.
Look at this.
I need to fill this with blood or something.
Is there already blood in here or did I kill something in there?
Oh yeah, I can go through walls.
Gotta remember that.
I gotta get back into gear here, you know?
Slow, slowly I'm gonna get back into it.
Blood up there.
Let's just focus on healing up first.
Plate ultra safe here.
Look at that.
Amazing.
Maybe we should get another blood bottle.
I should drink the rest from the floor.
Okay.
Hello.
Oh,
man, I wish you could get rid of these guys.
They're actually... it's the worst part about this area is these guys.
Because there's like nothing I can do about it.
Get away from me.
Okay, there's a bunch of blood.
This is good.
Except this guy is here, so that's annoying.
Let me get the money.
Money, money, money.
And then we get out.
Nice.
Okay, I'm gonna distract that guy down here.
What is that stuff right there?
Is that dangerous?
That's berserk him, no?
My guy, are you gonna... Whoa.
Whoa, sick dodge there.
Oh, nice.
Look at that.
A heart.
Very cool.
I thought I cleared most of this place, actually.
I guess I was wrong.
That guy.
Eat from the floor.
Are we gonna get another cloud on us?
Oh!
Murder.
Kill them all.
I have a pretty good wand here.
Maybe one of my best.
Okay, there's nothing up there.
What do we have here?
You know what?
Imagine, what if my slowing down of the game was to do with that third-party program I used to?
Imagine if that is now gone as well.
That would be incredible.
Because it did start quite late, right?
Like when I switched over to having the drawing stuff.
Maybe there was something going on there.
You never know.
I can only hope.
Oh yeah, I love this.
Give me all that blood.
And we leave.
I drink.
509 health.
That's so good.
That is a lot of blood, but also a lot of lava, and that scares me a little bit.
I can stand on this, right?
I should be okay.
Hopefully I won't die immediately if I fall in lava.
Oh, oh no, oh no.
I'm so scared of that thing.
Okay, grab some more from here.
We're gonna have to try and kill that monster.
We have to.
Okay, good.
That's big.
Don't eat from the floor when there's lava.
Oh, I just had a mini heart attack.
Holy shit.
Do not eat from the floor when there's lava.
At least I know I don't instantly die in it, you know?
Well, I think it's... Let's see, let's see.
Please tell me I can do damage.
Wait, that's it?
There's no way.
No way.
Really?
That's what I was scared of?
What a joke.
Whoop.
Hey!
What the fuck?
Guys, how crazy was that just now?
All my digging is paying off.
Get this, eat from the floor.
Slurp, slurp, slurp.
Come on.
Okay.
Oh.
Anything hiding in this pile?
Why is this guy so confused?
He doesn't come towards me now.
Very odd.
Get some blood here.
This is a lot of blood.
Dude, vampirism is insanity.
Full HP.
Full HP, baby.
And let's fill up the bottle just so we have a bit more.
He's coming towards me now.
But if I go over here...
Okay, he's still coming.
No, no.
Why is he not coming?
Come here.
What if I go over here?
It's like some invisible barrier.
Sir, why are you stuck?
What?
Why are you stuck?
Kill that guy who drops a bunch of bone dust.
Nice.
Hell yeah.
And then we drink the blood.
Full HP again.
Very good.
Oh, whoa, whoa.
Tell me that guy died.
He did.
Okay, good, good, good.
Shit.
That attack does a lot of damage.
Something hiding down here for me.
God, I love my digging wand.
It's the best digging wand I've ever had.
I mean, when it comes to non-dense stuff, you know?
Obviously, the plasma cutter is best.
Whoa, why shouldn't have clicked on that?
Actually, what does that just do?
That is not the earthquake one, right?
Oh, the... hold on.
I have to remind myself.
Is the green one the...
Curse?
It is.
Okay.
Green is curse.
Purple one is the explosion and something else is something else.
What?
Wrong wand.
I gotta get used to the keybinds here again.
Also, is my water bottle filling faster when the blood is flowing?
Feels that way.
There we go.
Some more blood.
Look at him.
Why are you scared?
I don't understand these things.
Are you willing to attack me now?
He's willing, I think.
No.
Wait, I see something in there.
Wait a minute.
There's something in there.
Oh, it looked like a spell.
It looked like a black hole spell through the fog.
Grab this blood.
Yo, where did these guys come from?
Weird.
Are they just patrolling?
Could be.
Show me secrets.
Wait, what's going on here?
Boom.
Collapsed concrete.
Brick work.
I gotta be on the lookout here.
There's some secrets here and there.
This is all cursed.
I've been up there.
Anything in that little...
You know, they're not that bad.
It's just annoying to have them follow you around, you know, because you can't really relax.
A purple crystal.
I think I've seen this one before.
Yeah.
Oh, that's a lot of mana.
Look at that.
2850.
Jesus.
Wow.
Anything hiding here?
God, the digging is so satisfying.
Ah, wait a minute.
What do we got here?
Nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope.
Surprise.
Look at all that blood.
There's healing for days there.
Have I ever run out?
I know where to go.
Well, I don't, but you know, I can't find my way back there, but at least I know there's a spot.
That's good enough for me.
Oh, nice little deflection there with my shield.
Where am I going now?
Who else wants some?
Nobody.
Oh, there we go.
Ah, just money.
I mean, I guess I kind of need money.
Yeah, let's not look at gift tours in the mouth here.
It was a gift after all.
Oh yeah, wait, wait, we needed money to reroll perks as well.
I think we needed 16,000.
I spent 8k on the last, I believe.
Or was it 4k?
Also, there's a want there.
I could go through here, but I'm scared of what's on the other side, so I can always go back.
Okay, nice.
A chili egg.
Oh, you know what?
Since that is located right there, what about we throw it in the lava?
A hymn is born and died.
Such is the circle of life in Neuter.
Ah, it's sad.
Ooh, oh yeah, that reminds me.
We gotta go try out that.
You know, I think I'll save my money for the perk reroll.
Right?
Wait, what?
Heplicate spell?
Oh, wait, I can't kill that guy.
Um, interesting.
No, I can't get through there.
Let's go down here.
What do these guys do?
Blue sand, right.
Oh, wait, it was buried in the blue sand.
Nothing.
What the fuck is the blue sand?
Blue sand.
There's yellow sand and there's blue sand.
Hold on, I want to release this slime.
Don't judge.
What?
Yo, that slime has some surface tension.
Hmm, that's very suspicious.
Uh, give me the money.
Can I get in there?
No.
Nice.
So what does this one do again?
That is the explosion.
The explosion.
Okay, watch this.
How cool is that?
Pretty dope, huh?
The green one is the curse.
Oh, a chest for me.
Didn't mean to do that, but okay.
What's in the pile?
Give me more hearts.
That is chaotic polymorphine.
Bad.
You don't want that.
Oh, yeah.
And over the blood.
I've been here before.
Actually, I guess that came from a...
What is the color of that?
I guess purpley, bluey crystal thing.
Whoa, my dude.
Calm yourself.
I must have cleared this entire place soon, huh?
I feel like I've killed so many things here.
Drink the blood.
Oh, hold on.
Oh, look at that.
Thought he could hide from me.
What's that?
Oh.
Wait, what?
Is that a perk?
You grow disturbing looking limbs that fight for you.
Uh, I don't know if I want that.
I had one of these things before and I hated it.
Remember?
What the hell?
I don't know if I should do it.
It's a perk.
Oh, you grow disturbing looking limbs that fight for you.
Leggy mutation.
I believe I had a lucky mutation at some point.
I don't think I want it.
Fuck off.
That sounds something like that.
I know I said it would try new things, but just not that one, please.
Anything but that one.
I don't want that.
I hated it so much last time.
I actually wanted to end the run like on purpose just to get rid of it.
Well, something like it, you know, it was Lukey, but still.
Whoa, what's happening here?
A lot of curse.
So, so that can be perks inside of chests.
That's kind of, that's nuts.
That really blows my mind.
Oh, hello.
Goodbye, you bastard.
And I want, uh, hey, sir, come here.
Come here.
Actually, wait a minute.
We're going to do this again.
Maybe there's a heart in there.
You never know.
Let's just do it like that.
Go.
Oh my God, there's so much sand.
Oh, I need to check that out.
Kill all that shit.
What do we got?
Uh, spells per cast nine.
Damn.
Remove bounce.
And normally bouncy projector.
Oh, that sounds awesome.
I want that.
Hello.
I, um, what was that one?
They could vacuum.
Uh, I'm kind of intrigued by that one still.
So maybe we get rid of, honestly, that one.
I don't want it.
Charm on toxic sludge.
No.
Fuck yeah.
Oh, wait a minute.
I need to... Ooh, that guy spits poison?
What the heck?
This place keeps throwing me curveballs.
And boy, am I good at returning them.
We have more blood here.
Lovely.
Get all that gold as well.
Kind of need gold.
This place is much bigger than I thought.
Oh, wait, I can dig through this shit?
Oh, no, I can't.
Okay.
What was that?
Why is it making... Why is it doing that?
Is that a, uh, circle of stillness or whatever?
Diggity, diggity, diggity, diggity, diggity, diggity.
Nothing.
Wow.
Okay.
Hello.
These bastards, man.
Oh, you know what?
I kind of want to try and, uh...
Whoa, hold on a second.
Hold that thought.
These guys are dangerous.
Okay, then we go up here.
Oh, man.
Okay, my game is still slowing down.
It's definitely the game.
I think I got him.
Also, we have, uh, explosion immunity.
That's big.
There's some more blood.
He's going to leave me alone for some reason.
I don't understand why they sort of do that.
There's a guy in there, a song.
I kind of want to collect this, uh, sand.
What's this?
Hey, you know what?
Hold on.
Throw this away, that away.
Let's just use these right now.
Let's make some paths.
Water.
Uh, why am I... Oh, I'm slimy.
I think I have poison on me.
No, I thought I had my digging wand.
I'm an idiot.
Oh, well, I guess I do, but it's a different digging wand.
Ah, I'm scared of leaving this here.
It's probably okay.
We can come back for that one.
I wonder if wands can get destroyed.
What if I black hole through a wand?
Will that actually destroy the wand?
I feel like we should try that just for fun.
What if I... Hold on.
I want to try something crazy here.
Oh, it's shuffled, so we got to do this.
What if I just do that?
I'm being a little crazy here now.
I'm gonna refresh these anyway.
It's fine.
This... Oh, wait, what?
Oh, this... I'm an idiot.
We should do this.
Oh, wait, this is kind of... Ah, it's fine.
Oh, it's low on mana.
Ah, that sucks.
Dude, you can... With the black hole, if you have enough, you can go fucking anywhere and you can go quick.
Wow.
I'm gonna... Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Be careful here.
Put this back.
In fact, I can put this here for now because it will conserve a slot up here, at least.
And it doesn't degrade from my wand, right?
Let's see.
Shit.
I forgot I had the black holes here.
Dang it.
It's fine.
Um... or even this one, actually.
Let's put this one here.
Now it never bounces.
How cool is that?
In fact, I think that's really cool.
And then let's replace that one.
Then we take our last wand back.
There we go.
I do wonder, like...
Okay.
You know what?
Hold on.
We have a new plan.
Why is it always so zoomed in when I switch over here?
It's so annoying.
We're gonna add something to the list.
We're gonna add...
Get a... lot of black holes.
No, that doesn't make sense.
Let me just write it out.
And dig...
forever.
Just to see what happens in some direction.
Direction.
Very good.
Let's see what else we got here.
What's up, man?
What's that?
Oh!
Teleportation.
I hate teleportation.
Whoa!
What's this?
Look at this place!
Another one?
Oh, what the hell?
Yo!
Oh, lava.
This is just rock.
I can dig through that.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I have an idea.
We're gonna do this.
Oh, wait.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Actually, no, no, no.
Because maybe there's something inside of here and I don't know what it is yet.
Don't destroy it in case there's something in there.
Black hole would eat that shit.
Just do that.
Let's just get in and see.
Obviously, don't go in the lava.
Why is there some lava in here?
What's that?
Okay, there's just rock and nothing.
That is interesting.
I can stand up here now and shoot.
It's gonna take a while.
There's obviously something going on here.
What's that?
Oh!
What is that?
It's a portal.
Ho Ho Ho Ho!
Portal to the tower?!
Wait, what's...
enter tower.
What the fuck?
Where am I?
We've got some Hamis people.
No, Heasy people.
Oh, god.
Oh god.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Yo, that guy has HP!
Up the wazoo!
He's getting a little fucked.
Wait, this looks like, uh...
This looks like the hemisphere.
Doesn't it?
Like a little bit?
It's a chest.
So, what is this place?
I'm so confused.
We gotta drink some blood.
Guys?
What's that?
Oh, it's one of those guys that spawn other guys.
They have a lot of HP actually in this place.
This is no joke.
What is that?
A gem?
Wait a minute.
See what?
Huh!
It's a gem!
Well, I'm gonna collect some blood.
Nice.
Just fill me up all the way.
Wait, I don't think I can... I gotta get rid of this gem.
Yeah!
There we go.
Get it out of there.
Wasn't that gem an enemy not too long ago?
Drink the blood.
Okay.
Sweet.
Actually, there's more here.
Just grab it all.
Doesn't matter if we get some slime in there.
It is what it is.
Slimy egg.
Oh, look at these things.
Sir?
Oh, wow!
HP on this guy.
Hold on.
Am I... Did I mess up my thing?
I feel like I'm not doing as much damage as I used to, guys.
I feel like I may have changed something here.
That's not good.
Hold on.
What have I done?
This used to do like 2,000 something damage.
I definitely changed something.
Let's just re-evaluate this wand right here.
One second, though.
Look at all that blood.
Actually, I'm gonna grab that real quick.
Oh, and it's so much better when it's fired, too.
I don't need to be drinking fire.
So nice.
Oh, wait.
I'm full HP.
Okay.
What did I change?
I guess I added this.
Wait, what?
Okay, let's try and understand.
Four?
One, two, three?
No, one, two.
Is it because I had a triple there instead of a...
No, this is a quadruple.
So I did add mana.
Chainsaw.
Damage plus.
So hold on.
So damage plus is being added to this right here, but this consists of four spells.
Did I have a... I think I had a triple here, and this is now messing it up.
Hmm.
Wait a minute.
Yeah, that's definitely not how it was.
It was definitely with this.
Adduce recharge time.
Is it the mana?
Maybe that's actually doing it.
Hold on.
Still very low DPS there.
I do not fucking realize what I changed.
Why do I keep drinking it?
I'm full HP.
It's a bad habit right now.
Okay, I'm somewhere else in my mind.
Uh, let's see.
Did I have an extra one of these maybe?
Actually that... that stack... no, that's about the same, isn't it?
Remember when I shot with this?
I used to do like 2000 something damage.
Like really fast.
Oh, that's a mess.
Let's try that.
Oh no, we need this for the digging.
That's... oh, that... oh, it's definitely slower with this.
Yeah, let's try that.
I think this is what I had before, but whatever.
Let's just rock with that for now.
And when we get to a point where it makes sense, we're gonna reevaluate the one situation.
So where the fuck are we right now?
The tower?
What does that even mean?
Uh, go up here.
Get rid of all these guys.
Is that mine?
It is.
Like, tell me this is not hemisphere.
Look at this.
It's like a different version of the hemisphere.
Oh, hello.
Okay, I feel like I'm doing more damage than before now.
Am I crazy?
Ooh.
Oh wait, is that the... oh, that's the same chest from before.
Thought it was another one.
Hey.
Sometimes when my mouse is up here, it's annoying because I want to aim at an enemy, but I click the buttons up here.
Uh oh.
Let's calm down.
Like, look at this.
How is this not the hemisphere?
Enemies.
But then not really.
There's also more, you know?
Oh, look at all this blood.
This is healing forever.
Pretty much full health.
Instantly.
Oh, that's cursed rock right there.
I don't like that.
Oh, look at this.
There's these types of enemies in here too.
Dude, I am beyond intrigued at where I am right now.
I wonder where I am in relation to everything else in the world.
Wait.
Oh no, what is this?
Fuck you.
Look at that.
I made a mountain of rock because he was bleeding lava while there was water in the air.
Hold
on.
Before I go this way, I kind of want to explore left first.
Let's take it really slow here.
We don't know what we're going to find.
What's going on in there?
Let me take care of you guys.
Lovely.
Wait, is this...
This looks like, uh, what should I call it?
The coal mines.
Coal pits.
What is that?
Dude, this guy does not die.
Did I hear a shotgun man?
I did.
Oh, oh.
This guy won't die, dude.
Look at the spells orbiting him.
I'm getting a lot of gold though.
That's nice.
Oh my god, finding gold like this is nuts.
Emergency teleport out of there.
Another thing this one is great for.
What is that?
What is going on?
Look where we are now.
We're in the snowy depths now.
It's like a miniature version of the entire, uh, progression.
Very weird.
Who are you?
The fuck was that?
Please die.
Wow.
That blood though.
What just happened?
Why was there so much?
I don't get it.
Oh, I touched the rock.
Don't touch the cursed rock.
Do not touch the cursed rock.
You know what?
Fill a water bottle.
I kind of forgot that that was empty.
I'm a worm.
Vampirism is one of the best perks in the game.
Changed my damn mind.
I have so much money.
Soon I can go back.
Well, can I?
I was about to say we can go back and grab those perks, but now I'm not so sure.
Like, uh, how are we going to get back?
Anything down here?
Grab some blood.
Okay.
So the very bottom part is hemisphere.
And then we go up and the next part is cold pits.
It's like, uh, a miniature version, but in reverse.
So weird.
I'm intrigued.
I'm very intrigued.
There's 100% going to be a boss up at the top, no?
Uh-oh.
I hear electricity.
At least these enemies are like, I guess the same enemies that we had in these regions.
So it's actually kind of easy.
Except there were a couple different ones that were a little bit harder.
Like that, you know?
Let me just see if I got everything here.
I did not.
Oh, this guy is shooting a frost at me.
And he bleeds snow.
Excuse me.
He died.
Oh.
Don't touch the rock.
Shotgun dude.
What do you want?
And look, he's the base.
Uh...
What is that?
Also, friendo?
Do we get...
Oh, you know what I think?
I think this is a buffer.
Wait, what?
Blue sand?
Is that making the enemies, uh, ghosts?
Oh, that's right!
We got this last time too!
And I'm not sure what it means.
Oh yeah, look, you'll look.
Yeah, definitely a buffer.
It gives them protection or like invincibility or something.
Phasing or, you know?
What the fuck is that?
That's burning whiskey!
Uh...
Wait, what are you?
Motherfucker.
I remember this dude.
I don't remember where we saw him, but...
Hold on.
Can we mess with him somehow?
What if we dig on him?
Hey!
You're like, you're like, you're like, that!
Okay, wow, this guy is...
Fisticuffs type of person, huh?
Hmm, what if we water him?
Like that?
Okay, how do you like music?
What if I play a tune for you?
Hey, listen to this, listen to this track right here.
This is the shit, right?
No?
Okay.
Okay, now he lost interest.
Oh, wait a minute, these guys actually, uh, were on my side sometimes, remember?
Last time I met one, he fought for me.
But I guess he fights everyone then.
He does not distinguish.
Oh, another one.
Maybe he wants whiskey?
Let's grab some.
Hey, sir, drink, drink up my lad.
Oh, he's drunk now!
Look at that!
Massive drunk.
Yo, what if I, can I make my enemies high?
Think about it.
Aiming is disturbed and alcohol is, oh, actually, I shouldn't be drunk.
Drunk is bad.
So, there's two enemies so far that I know of that I can't hurt.
It's the massive ghosts and these fucking...
Like Lodad!
He, uh, he kills enemies for me.
And he can't die.
Oh, but wait a minute, maybe we can charm him!
Pheromone.
Uh, that guy looks a little scary.
I have just the recipe though.
Oh no, not with this guy here.
Get out of here.
Hehehe!
Oh!
Right, okay.
See ya.
No, no!
I want to find friendo.
Oh, now we're in the jungle.
That is so mystical, isn't it?
What's that?
Brass plus fungal?
Soil plus weird fungus pouch?
Hmm.
I want!
Wow.
Yeah, you can keep that one.
I'm sorry.
That's not that great.
Someone has a want down here, I think.
Wait, what?
I think he has ambrosia on him.
How did he get that?
They're all blocking.
This is so cool.
Long distance cast.
Doesn't look like fire does anything to him either.
In fact, I need to do this just for my own sanity here.
Uh, yeah, that's fine.
Wait, he doesn't see me?
Or maybe it's because he's drunk.
He doesn't give a crap about me.
Oh, see that easy.
Such a weird mix of enemies from all the regions here.
That's a crystal.
So the way it's a crystal.
Uh, look at that!
Oh!
Okay, okay, okay.
All right, all right, all right, all right, come down.
What the fuck is going on?
Oh, that guy is nuts!
Okay.
Oh, wait, we have another buffer somewhere.
Where are you?
Kill that dude.
Get rid of this thing.
There we go.
What the fuck is this up here?
Uh, is that a god?
Gods are enraged?
He spawns little thingies.
What the hell?
Let's go kill him.
Oh, I'm scared.
Oh, that's right!
You're mad now, bruh!
Why does that message keep popping up?
I don't like that.
Also, I think I see the buffer.
Oh, and there's a heart in there.
Let's not forget it.
My god, man.
Okay, let's take it easy here.
Take it easy.
Oh, wait, are we immune to acid?
We're not.
It's only toxic.
So, we should be fine in here, right?
Hey!
We swim in toxic sludge!
Look at all this blue sand.
Mysterious blue sand.
Hello!
What's up, my dudes?
I want to go back and get perks now.
How do I get back?
Okay, prediction.
When we get to the top of this place, there's going to be a portal back home.
It's like a little mini dungeon, I think.
Or maybe I'm just hoping there will be.
That's fine.
We don't care about toxic.
Oh, not these guys.
I need to figure out exactly how they work.
Like, you can only hit their face and they take super little damage.
Wait, what is that?
Steel?
Wow.
Okay.
Oh, that's molten!
That's bad, that's bad.
We got to find blood.
Let's play this safe.
I want to find a big pool of blood.
I think we had some down here, a big one.
Somewhere.
That works.
Oh, man.
Look at all the goo, all the blood.
Here we are.
That's what I'm talking about.
Dude, this run has gone places I never expected.
I was going to go up to the fucking laboratory and all that.
But instead, I'm here.
Doing God knows what in a weird ass region, and I actually love it.
More blood, more blood, more blood.
Still want to go to that dark cave.
That's why I'm carrying around this goddamn worm blood.
Like, I'm ready, baby.
I'm ready.
I've been ready.
All right, let's go.
That's flammoxium.
I can tell by the pattern and from having seen quite a few flammoxiums in my time.
This is so insane.
Like, look at this.
I can go anywhere I want.
Doesn't even fucking matter.
I am unstoppable.
Wait,
is that toxic?
It's cursed.
Every...
Like, both sides.
I wonder if you can dig through that.
Like, if I end up being stuck here...
Look, it's still cursed.
What's up, dude?
Nice!
I'm healing.
Oh, no.
You've got another one of those fucked up freaks up here.
It's like an uki on drugs.
Or is it uku?
Uki uku?
Where are you, sir?
Oh, he's up there.
I think.
Yeah, that's definitely him.
So watch this.
This is the strategy, okay?
This is why this is so good.
Oh, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait.
I did the wrong thing.
Wait, what?
There we go!
Nice!
The safe way to dispose of these enemies.
Amazing.
What's that?
I saw a laser.
Oh, hello.
What?
Oh, no, oh, no.
It's absorbing everything.
Do we do this?
Is that the trick here?
Watch this.
We go right through his shield now, baby.
Sir?
Whoa.
I need to be closer.
I need to see exactly when it's like that distance.
Okay, okay.
It's like...
It doesn't work!
Teleport!
I don't know what to do.
Huh, let me think.
So he's all electric and shit.
What about water?
Okay, he doesn't care.
What about music?
If I play you a tune?
Listen to these tunes, boy.
No, you don't like the tunes.
Okay.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God.
Also, I just realized I need to switch this back.
Okay, for now, I just avoid that guy, I guess.
What's that?
Oh, it's teleportation.
Oh, there's a crystal.
Yeah, get up there.
Look at that guy, half a shield.
Well, avoiding him seems okay for now.
But running from my problems is not going to work forever, right?
That's what I think.
Uh-oh, he's coming.
This is getting a little bit too tricky.
Grab some blood while we can.
Maybe we get high.
Forget about our problems.
It's a solution.
Fuck, what do I do, man?
Let me think.
Maybe we...
Maybe we dig on him.
You like some dig?
You like dig?
Wait, where's that up here?
Oh, it's appearing right.
Oh, that's not what I want, actually.
I want to be able to dig exactly when...
I need a trigger, basically.
Need a trigger.
I need a trigger.
I don't have it.
Crap.
Unless, long distance, dig.
Oh, no!
No!
Wait, does he not...
Wait, does he even do anything to me?
Hold on, let's chill for a moment.
Oh, he's stuck.
Wait a second.
Let me see.
Okay, so when I shoot him, it causes an electric explosion.
Hmm.
Causes an electric explosion.
I feel like water may be the way.
Or not.
Fuck me, man.
I'm just gonna ignore him.
Hopefully, he goes away if I go far enough and fast enough.
Is he coming?
Leave me alone.
Maybe he did.
Maybe he's gonna...
I know what to do!
Watch this!
Oh, this is genius.
I'm a goddamn genius.
Hey, motherfucker!
Come here!
Let's have some fun!
Up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up.
Hey!
Come here!
I need to be careful not to get hit by this myself.
That's the one...
That's the big thing here.
What?!
It did nothing!
Wow, okay!
That guy does not care about anything!
Uh,
what's happening?
Why am I...
Oh, that's weird.
What's that?
Gold?
Oh, gold noggin.
Okay.
Oh!
I didn't even realize I blinked into that.
Amazing!
Cool.
The most accidental, uh, hard pickup ever.
The next step is pheromone.
Pheromone should do the trick.
I need an empty bottle for that, though.
Or just get rid of one of my...
Or maybe worm blood I can get rid of.
Let's grab some blood here.
We need to heal a bit.
Wait, what's happening?
Oh, he's a friend.
Actually, there's polymorphine down there.
Okay.
Give me blood.
Drink the blood.
I think I lost him for now.
Man.
Maybe these guys!
Maybe I can have these guys follow me up there and kick his ass.
Come here.
What's that?
Oh, it's slime.
Oh, but you can't go through walls, though, can you?
That's the issue.
That is... What is that?
Pheromone.
Ooh.
Let's take some.
Oh, you're my friend now.
Except you're not.
You don't...
No, you're not my friend.
Pheromone and these guys does nothing.
Okay.
Hey, look!
Look at that!
It's working!
Kill him!
Kick his ass!
Yeah!
Street Fighter!
That's it!
I'm gonna take a sip right now and just enjoy the sh- Uh...
He died.
Uh, sir?
Will you please go on the enemy?
He's right over there, come on.
This is such a- You know what?
Maybe the way to do this is to just go with a- What about a black hole?
Can we come consume him?
Maybe he's the one enemy that can be consumed by that.
Oh, I need to get rid of this guy first.
He's annoying me.
Ah, let's see here.
What else do we have at our disposal?
Uh, we could try this.
That freezes things.
Let's try that.
Maybe he doesn't like that.
Let's get some blood.
Where are you?
Look how everything gets frozen now.
What if I freeze diamonds?
Oh, they become solid.
I think the guy's gone, at least for now.
No, wait, he's up there.
Fuck.
Will you leave me alone, man?
Please.
Let's just heal up.
I could get high, but I've decided not to do that in this run.
How am I taking damage?
Wait, why is this not- Wait a minute, is this not digging through because of the frost thing?
Are you gonna hit me while- while-
Okay, never mind.
I thought he could hit me while he was pheromone, but I guess not.
That's good to know, actually.
Oh, it's because it's steel?
I thought it was ice because I froze it.
I just confused myself completely.
Oh, here we go, here we go.
Delicious blood.
Oh, that's polymorphine.
I don't like polymorphine.
Makes me uneasy.
Damn it.
I hate getting polymorphed.
Blood me up.
Drink.
Okay, let's go.
Is he gonna be gone?
Please be gone.
Please- oh, oh wait, I have to grab this again.
Forgot about my note.
Okay.
Oh, this guy.
I know how to deal with you.
Wait, why are you blocking?
There we go.
Easy peasy.
Nice.
I can water this a bit.
That's fine.
Whoa, what was that?
Wait, Wills is shooting.
Ah, we've got one of those thingies somewhere.
Where did that come from?
I have to remember, I can always just do this.
The world is my oyster.
With this digging capability that I possess.
What did I just do?
Oh, hello there.
Mysterious person.
Thou art dead.
I'm looking for blood.
A lot of blood, not just a little bit.
I need a shit ton of it.
Ooh.
Waiting for me, huh?
We have been that way.
Oh, I wand.
Oh, wait, what?
It's inside that rock.
Wait, what?
Oh, it's that guy.
He's stuck.
Let's leave him there.
Yep, we don't engage.
Oh, wait, what?
Hold on, can I?
Let's do this.
Like that.
Oh, yeah.
What the fuck?
It's just...
Okay, confirmed.
It does not eat the wand.
That's actually a big discovery.
Oh, what?
Just being near it hurts.
I thought you had to touch it.
Oh, no.
Oh, I don't like that.
I don't know if I should waste my shit on this.
Hmm.
It's a black hole with death triggered that eats through all obstacle and casts another spell as it expires.
Are we fine now?
Let's do one more.
Wow, I still take damage.
Accelerating shot.
Deadly heal.
Plasma beam.
Healing bolt.
That's good.
Another black hole.
That's actually...
Oh, man, I'm taking damage from that.
That's scary stuff.
Put that up there.
You know what?
We can replace some of these.
Fuck these.
This one seems better, right?
So let's just put that there.
This one can stay.
Matter eater makes a projectile eat the environment as it flies.
Venomous curse.
Chaos larva.
Why would I do this?
Oh, maybe it makes it faster in the beginning, but then it slows down, I guess.
Better for short range spells or something that expires quickly?
Okay.
I don't want the rest.
Although...
No, I don't want the rest.
All right, let's leave this guy alone.
Let's go find some healing.
Man, you cannot be near any of this.
Phew.
Cursed.
Rock is really cursed.
So now we are in the vault.
Well, it seems to be the vault, but what the hell?
Is that a fox?
Look at that.
Kill them all.
Oh, wait.
Hold on.
That's why it didn't work.
Oh, wait, I was so confused there for a second.
Now I understand what was happening.
I still had these here.
Let's throw this there.
Don't want that.
In fact, I do want this one, but not one of these.
What is that sound I'm hearing?
Where's the buffer?
Oh, god.
Show thyself.
There it is.
See ya.
Wait, what?
Huh, I want...
Okay, so the gods are enraged.
I think that just means they spawn randomly and chase you now.
It's not just in the holy mountain.
They're everywhere.
They're trying to chase you down and make you pay for your crimes.
They've had enough.
Still cursed everywhere.
I don't like that.
Makes me feel bad.
Oh, no.
Not these guys.
That's Ambrosia.
I can't die.
You want to come kick me?
You can't.
I'm gonna kick you.
Hey, you want some...
Nice.
Murder that dude.
Whoop.
Let's be careful here.
I need to find...
You know what?
Hold on.
I'm playing this safe.
I'm going down.
I gotta find blood.
Not that way.
Down here was a lot.
God, this teleport one is amazing.
All the way down.
I know where...
Oh, here we go.
Here we go.
Nice.
I don't have to go all the way down.
That's great.
Oh, hold on.
Nice.
Some more blood.
Very good.
It's feeding time.
Oh, I drank all this.
I thought I had more left over here.
I guess I didn't.
Oh, don't touch the cursed rock.
Ah, here we go.
Here we go.
Is that toxic sludge?
I don't care.
I can drink that.
I'm immune.
Or am I?
Actually, I'm not.
Plumsy movement.
Oh, overeating?
I thought blood didn't...
I must have eaten something else.
No.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What's happening?
Hold on.
This only contains blood, right?
Yeah, this doesn't affect it.
If there's something else in there, then it goes wrong.
Let's be careful not to pick anything else up.
Only blood.
I think I picked something else up.
Dang it.
Why is it follow me?
Okay, that works.
Almost full health.
I think if I drink water, that counts to overeating.
There's 6% water in here.
Yeah, see?
Long as I don't pick up water, it should be okay.
Nice.
Full health.
That's a big deal, actually.
Never just did that.
Okay, up we go.
What a weird place.
Here.
There.
Ah, dang it.
I hate that.
Just change me back, please.
There we go.
Okay.
I am so tempted to get high.
Not gonna do it, though.
I have the resistance of an ox.
Everyone knows oxes are very resistant to the allure of highness.
I don't know what the fuck I'm talking about.
Oh, you there.
What?
This is the only place I've seen these guys.
It's a new monster.
Wait, what's going on in there?
Oh, I don't trust it.
Huh?
Did I get him?
Whoever you are.
Oh, was it a crab?
All the blood?
I mean, all the oil?
Show me the secrets hidden within.
Okay.
Or not.
Oh, you know what?
I'm gonna do the same thing.
Sup, fool?
Such a wild wand.
Easy.
Switch it back.
Oh, nice.
Ooh, that's a lot of lava.
What was that?
Hellrock?
Wait, where am I?
Am I in hell?
Sure looks like it.
And I'm overeating.
What the fuck is this?
I can't dig through it.
I can't dig.
There's lava everywhere.
Oh, what?
Hey.
Wait, I can dig through it?
Oh, hell slime.
Come here.
Oh, nice.
The weight bounced off.
Cool.
Where the...
It's a whole new biome.
I can't believe this.
This is crazy.
Dude.
Oh, imagine if I get to pick perks at the end of this.
Who's that?
Whoever you were, you're dead.
I think it was a crab.
Giving all the oil.
Close it up.
What the actual crap?
That guy shot pollen.
Oh, no.
We've got more fisticuff people.
Oh, hello.
I know how to deal with you.
See ya.
Hee hee hee hee hee hee.
Ah, ah.
Fuck, ah.
Hold on, I wasn't done exploring this part.
We're not done here.
No, sir.
Is that...
That's ambrosia.
Kind of want to bring some.
But it's kind of hard to pick up when there's such a little amount of it.
What?
Oh, it's the...
It's the cursed rock.
The cursed rock is doing it once again.
Yeah, don't be close to it.
Question is, can I find any blood up here?
This is really not where I want to be.
In fact, it's where I really want to be.
I mean, I wasn't planning on going here of all pla- Am I taking damage?
No, I'm hurting something.
Wait, what did I just hurt?
Also, eating slime gives me...
Oh, you don't want to eat slime.
Slime makes you really full.
Don't eat slime, people.
Also, don't eat slime, people.
Whoops.
Oh, that's bad.
Mix it up.
Cleanse the next room.
I need to find another long-distance cast.
It is way too much fun.
Oh, shit.
What a place.
And now we get to a new area again.
What the hell?
Wait a minute.
What is going on here?
There's gotta be secrets in this place, man.
There's just gotta be.
Um, how about we don't release that llama?
Look at the hellrockets composed of skulls.
Music stopped.
Wait, is that...
Is that because there's a god?
Where are you?
Uh-oh.
Oh?
Never mind.
Wait a minute.
Ah!
What did I say?
Okay, I don't know if it'll lead me back, but I think it will.
What did I fucking say?
What's inside of here, though?
Oh, what?
Want?
It has a want of multitudes.
Want of destruction?
Wait, recharge time minus 38?
Want of swiftness.
Holy shit!
I can make the craziest wants!
Wait, wait, wait.
Which one should I get for what?
I'm gonna...
Dude, I can use this one for...
Oh, I get all these spells?
I kind of want this stat, though.
Hold on, let me get this.
Ah, okay.
I had a feeling maybe it would only be one.
I was hoping it wouldn't be, but this is fine.
This is fine.
This is what I wanted.
Look at these stats, dude.
Look at these stats!
I'm totally happy with this.
No, no.
Um, hold on, hold on.
Take these, put it here.
There.
Oh, man.
That is wild, boy!
Let me put everything in here for now.
That's...
Wait a minute, let's just see how this works.
I mean, it's pretty much the same, but infinite mana recharge on that.
Let me remove this, see if that even...
Okay, we definitely need mana on that, still.
I'll get rid of that one, and maybe even that one.
Do we even need that?
Look at this fucking stats on this.
It's wild!
Uh, yeah, we need mana.
And...
Let's see here.
It has minus 0.33 cast delay.
That means we have 0.33 cast delay as a buffer to work with.
So we add a bit of cast delay here, we add some there, that's 26.
And we add eight more, so that's...
What is that?
And then we remove some...
No, that's recharge time.
So pretty much zero.
And look at the recharge time, it's 0.05.
With this one, it's zero.
So it's pretty much instant.
It is instant.
Very sick.
Wow.
Okay, but let's try this one then, since it came with the wand.
I mean, that's kind of dope.
I guess.
Although the recoil on that is wild.
I don't know if I'm a fan of the recoil.
That's a bit too much recoil for me.
But why not both?
Actually, let's try that.
Then we go with all three, maybe.
Hey, hey, we actually run out of mana, but the recharge is so fast anyway.
Oh, come on, don't fall down.
Don't fall down.
Let's grab these as well.
We don't have any room, so let's do this for now.
There you go.
So what should I put in?
This can be another storage wand.
No, no, we need digging.
So let's do this.
And that's...
and just a good old digging.
But even better now.
You know what, I have so many black holes, I don't fucking want it.
Get rid of him.
I'll have three.
That seems about right.
I need space.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, this still digs like a motherfucker.
Look at that.
Oh, that's beautiful.
And the funny thing is, look at that.
The digging takes place a little further away from my character now because the wand itself physically is bigger.
Isn't that cool?
It happens at the end of the wand.
Hmm.
I could...
Oh, wait a minute.
I could do stuff like this now.
Question, do I want to do that?
Do I want to do that?
Runs out of mana very fast with that.
But I do have an extra add mana.
I could potentially do this.
And I'm pretty much full mana.
Oh, my lord.
Wow.
Okay, so I understand this.
You see how slow it is now?
The reason is that this casts four spells.
One, two, three, four.
If I remove this, it casts one, two, three.
And the next spell is...
Not that, not that, not that.
It is all the way here.
No, wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
Let me see.
One, two, three.
And then it casts the next spell, which is that one.
Chainsaw.
And chainsaw has modifier add mana on it.
Which means it has both.
So that means chainsaw is being used twice here.
So we get much faster.
Shoot.
See that?
When we get to a board, I'll prove it to you.
Okay.
This is amazing.
Dude, I was spot on with my prediction about this being like a mini dungeon and you get to go home after.
Why was it called Hell Rock, though?
That's very weird.
Wait a minute.
What's going on here?
Oh, what is that?
Burst of air.
What?
Uh...
Okay, do I need to use it here?
There's text.
What does that say?
Hold on.
I can't read that.
That is not, that is not English.
That is some kind of bullshit.
Do we need to fill this with some kind of liquid?
I kind of want to fill this with something, but I don't know what.
Yet.
What the hell?
Look at the shape of this.
It's diamond brickwork.
Let's think about this.
Who bleeds diamond?
The electricity enemies.
So something electricity related maybe goes in here.
I'm not quite sure.
Oh, or actually, no, no, no, no.
We fill it with diamonds.
We get a pouch and fill it with diamond.
We complete the shape.
Oh, oh, dude.
We fill it with diamond and then we freeze it to make it solid.
How about that?
Oh, huh?
We need a pouch though.
I think I saw a pouch somewhere.
Oh, the question is where the hell is that pouch?
It could be anywhere.
Actually, let's just explore this place a little bit more anyway.
We haven't explored everything here and I want to find that pouch.
Oh, wait a minute.
Also, let me do this stuff like this.
Maybe there's a heart in here.
Okay.
Pouch me up before I...
Ooh, maybe blue sand.
Ah, but I can't...
Can I eat blue sand?
I cannot eat blue sand.
Oh, that's a big pile of blue sand and bone dust and slime and...
Wow, what a mountain.
Man,
I kind of want to get high.
Should we get high?
Is that crazy?
No, we're still not doing it.
Oh, this guy.
What if I'm supposed to lead this guy back to the thing?
Think about it.
He's the only guy who can't die.
Well, as far as I know.
Could be an option.
No, I need to find that pouch.
Where could it be?
Hold on, let me think.
Where was...
Where did I see the pouch?
It was...
I think it was the very beginning of this level, actually.
The very beginning.
I give no fucks.
I just dig.
Isn't this amazing?
Teleportation.
And this is...
Oh, this is extremely...
Hold on.
Hold your horses.
This is not cursed.
Also, I need to heal.
Let's get some blood wobble here.
Don't get the water.
Fill it up more.
Okay, let's find this pouch.
I think it was somewhere in this region right here.
19k money, by the way.
Oh, it was not over there.
I think it was somewhere here.
Or was it here?
Cold pits.
Cold pits is not that big, it seems.
Thank God we have the teleport, huh?
Makes this a lot easier.
It is a little bit harder to dig with the wand digging further away from me.
A bit of a disadvantage on that.
I just want to grab this gold.
Why not?
Are we hiding in here?
Nothing but...
Oh, here we go, here we go.
Diamonds.
I cannot pick them up with a...
I need a pouch.
Need a pouch, pouch, pouch, pouch, pouch.
I...
Actually, hold on.
I think I remember where it is now.
It was in the jungle.
Jungle, jungle, jungle, jungle.
I'm pretty sure.
Somewhere here, somewhere here.
Is this one?
No, wait, that's not it.
It's somewhere...
What's that?
Purple crystal?
Say what?
Oh, okay.
Whatever.
Wand there.
Oh, here it is.
Found it!
Yes, sir!
Watch...
I may just get rid of...
Worm blood.
I can always get...
You know what?
I can get worm blood later on, because I can always grab the worm egg.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's leave that here.
Gently put it down on the ground.
There we go.
Oh, that's...
I can't see that at all.
It needs to have a place at least where I can see it.
Damn it!
Brass plus weird fungus plus fungal soil pouch.
Yep.
Let's just plant some fungi wherever we go.
What if I put fungi on toxic rock?
Just empty it completely.
And we go over here to collect the diamond.
Dude, I'm so right about this.
Watch.
This is gonna be the most insane thing.
Uh, it was down here, I think.
Ah.
This is like the fourth time I do this in this exact spot.
God damn it, Oliver.
Also, I should be careful.
There's fire right there.
Okay, here we go.
Here we go.
Oh, wait.
It's filled with all kind of crap.
Yeah, yes, it works!
Except there's also other stuff in here.
Oh, it's mostly diamond.
Perfect.
Mostly diamond, baby.
In fact, let me check quickly.
So right now it's 97% diamond and somehow 4% snow.
That's over 100.
But besides that, if I shoot it now, will it empty the least one first?
I guess it prioritizes...
Perfect.
Confirmed.
Get rid of that snow.
That is fine.
That's all we need.
Up we go.
Oh, hello.
Uh, go this way.
Just hiding like that.
Hold on, that's actually stuff I haven't explored here.
Bone dust.
Ah, here we go.
Oh, I don't have it.
I think I need to do multiple runs here.
Look at that!
It's perfect!
Oh, I'm so right about this.
And then we're gonna make it solid after.
Hold on, there's actually a bit of crap in the way here.
Fill it up.
Look how bright it is!
Almost blindingly so.
So watch this.
No, no, wait, wait.
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna get a bit more.
Let's find the best path there.
What's that?
Bone dust.
Ah, that's not exactly what I'm looking for.
Steel...
Oh!
Hello.
There's some diamond here.
Will you leave me alone, sir?
Please, get away from me, get away from me!
You motherfucker!
Why does he want to kick me?
Come here.
Okay.
Not bad.
Let's see how much we have.
That's good enough.
We can even empty it a little bit.
Now we only have diamond.
Beautiful!
Imagine if that portal takes me to the next stage...
of the mini dungeon.
And I'm not done yet.
Look at that beautiful sight.
Oh, yeah.
Now I wonder, though, if I need to fill it up all the way to the edge.
Or if I need to complete the square, so to speak.
Like, all the way up here, you see that?
Hmm.
Let me get one more round.
Or two more.
We'll have to see.
This guy's still here.
Ah, man.
Fuck off!
Heh.
There's actually a bunch of diamond there.
I'm gonna take that.
Is there something else in there?
Oh, some moss.
That's fine.
Whoop.
Did I hit some teleportation?
What just happened?
Say what?
I must have, yeah.
Ah, I keep touching the cursed shit.
Get away from me!
Wait, where's the rest of the diamond?
Wasn't there a huge pile?
Is it really the only...
No way.
Get all the diamond.
Also, I'm on fire now.
This is all great.
I'm losing all my HP here.
I think we may have enough.
72%.
Hold on, where's the big pile of diamond?
There was a big pile of it somewhere.
Not here.
Ah, here we go.
There's some here.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, we got all kinds of stuff in there we don't want.
Let's get rid of some of it.
Now it's pure.
You basically keep doing this.
You can actually tell just by the animation when it's pure.
Now it's pure.
Ah, almost.
That's good enough.
Let's go.
Long distance teleport is an absolute game changer for me.
Ever since discovering that, my game has improved so much.
What?
Shit, I accidentally put some contaminants in there.
We cannot have this shit contaminated.
Nice.
Okay.
And now comes the best part.
Come on.
This may actually almost precisely fill it up with three pouches.
If that isn't a sign, I don't know what is.
Look at this.
It's like perfect.
Well, almost.
Hold on.
Okay.
And now?
Now we do this.
Oh, wait a minute.
I should probably...
What should I use on it, though?
I don't want to dig through it.
Maybe this?
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
We need a...
This is not going to do anything, is it?
Almost.
Look at this.
Okay, it doesn't work.
Okay, fine.
All right, it doesn't work.
I tried.
I thought for sure I had to complete the fucking thing.
Whatever.
Put this here.
Put these back.
Wait.
Right, that's fine.
And this one.
There we go.
All right, let's just jump through here.
Or should I?
Wait a minute.
Hold on.
I'm not done.
Let's go where there's no cursed rock.
Like, look.
Oh, okay, the cursed rock starts there.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, wait a minute.
Ah, interesting.
That's where you were hiding, you little bastard.
And look at that.
That's a heart.
Beautiful.
Amazing.
Now we go.
What else could go in here?
I wonder.
Diamond.
Diamond brickwork.
And it contained a spell.
It contained puff of air.
Or burst of air.
Contained burst of air.
Air.
What is air made of?
Oxygen.
Nitrogen.
Do I need some kind of...
Do I need...
We have earth, wind, fire.
All those elements, right?
Wind is one of the elements.
Maybe I need to put another...
I don't know.
Fuck it, let's move on.
What?
No way we're here.
Wait, did I never pick that up?
I guess I didn't.
I must have started with a bomb or something.
What the hell?
That's amazing!
Oh!
Fuck yeah, dude!
That feels amazing!
Dude.
Oh!
Oh, because I picked up the orb.
Gotcha.
Hold on.
I want to explore this place in detail now.
I want to find all the hearts I never found.
And we don't have the worm, though.
I should have taken the worm stuff with me before we left.
No, wait.
No, I broke that one.
Anyway, it doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter.
I broke it.
Look at this.
We can just dig anywhere.
The hemisphere has never been the same.
Yeah.
I actually don't like the digging on this wand.
Because it's so long.
It is actually too long.
I like my old one.
Sup, guys?
Man, I haven't even explored this part of the hemisphere.
I wonder if I was that weak at this point that I just moved on.
Now we can get some healing on or done.
What is that in there?
Oh, it's gold.
I see.
Wait.
How did I just...
I feel like I just multiplied the blood somehow.
What did I just do?
You see that?
Drink it.
Weird.
Oh.
Like, watch this.
Okay, maybe not there, but...
I definitely multiplied the blood.
A frogster and a...
Look at that!
Yoink!
Thank you very much.
Whoa.
Pretty dope.
What is that?
Acceleration?
Um...
No, you know what?
I'm going to keep my pouch in case I want to pick up something.
Let's pick up some coal.
Eh?
Let's start experimenting a bit with this pouch.
Just pick up a bunch of shit.
Not that I know what to do with the coal, but, you know, I think it would be cool to do.
Am I doing really little damage here?
No!
I accidentally threw my blood.
That is a real big mistake right there.
We should be able to find, uh, another bottle, though.
For now, I'm just going to drink the fire.
Don't care.
In fact, I'm going to drink the toxic sludge.
No, I'm not.
I regret my actions.
Don't drink the...
Hold on.
There it is.
That's my potion.
I may just use all of this right now, and then just go fill up with blood.
When I find a bigger blood pool, of course.
And there we have a portal!
Uh...
Fuck you, sir!
Wow, wow, wow.
These guys ain't shit.
Oh, hello.
Oh, it's such a power feeling coming back here and kicking these guys' asses.
Oh, I love it.
I'm on a trip right now.
Make a big, nice basin.
Cool.
Oh, this one is going to be shit, isn't it?
Hey!
It's actually not shit.
A black hole for me.
I shall take it.
Much appreciated.
Yeah, this digging one is not very great right now.
I need another one for this.
I mean, it's fine, you know?
It's like, I'm just really picky right now.
That's really what it is.
Okay, let's not drink from the floor.
Let's be a little civilized here at least.
I don't think I enjoy the kickback on this.
Like, that is so much more comfortable to shoot with.
It may do a little less damage, but it's a prize I'm willing to pay.
I want it for me.
Oh, I'm stuck.
No, I...
No, I'm an idiot.
I shot some kind of projectile and I messed up the flask.
That's funny.
Disgusting.
What do we got?
A bubble spark?
Don't mind if I don't.
Oh, wait a minute.
Did I just destroy something?
Hold on.
I just made a bunch of blood.
I think I understand what's happening now.
Also, get this gold.
Like, look at that.
I made blood on the way down.
Did I make blood there?
All right, let's go to the cave.
Flammoxium stands in my way.
I was not a feared though.
Oh my god, I can't dig through the roots.
How rude.
No pun intended.
So, we can dig through this rock.
Actually, actually, we can just go grab some blood.
What the fuck am I on about here?
Grab some blood.
Don't make it harder than it needs to be.
Oh god.
Wait.
Oh no.
I need to be on the right side.
Come on.
Oh no, there's roots here too.
Oh, the roots are everywhere.
Those are roots here.
This is one big tree.
Wait.
Oh.
Wait a minute.
Where's that?
Ah.
Never mind.
Put this here, please.
What?
Where's my worm?
What a scam.
Oh, there you are.
Give me that worm, blood.
Worm, blood, hunt, hunt.
Ow!
Didn't even see you there.
Menace.
What the fuck?
Where did you guys come from?
Yo, this is toxic land.
Okay, whatever.
You guys do you.
That's cool.
I respect it.
Okay, here we go.
Here we go.
You see that?
I made blood.
Oh wait, I can just do this.
Nice.
10, 20.
Oh wait, hold on.
See, that's different.
That's a heal there.
That's a heal.
Is there anything else in here?
Is it always one of each?
I think it may be.
Pretty cool.
Okay, it's time.
Let's go here, man.
Copper.
Hold on, can I?
They are destroyable.
Last time I was here, I just had such a shitty weapon.
I didn't do anything to them.
Remember?
I thought you couldn't kill them because I just didn't have the damage.
Uh-oh.
This guy has protection on.
Sir, why do you have protection on?
This guy also has it.
Hmm.
Can't get through there.
What's up, dude?
Oh wait, is that?
Whoops.
Okay, sir.
I got one of them.
Why are they protected?
I don't understand.
Oh, wait.
Yeah, he came alive.
You see that?
Um, I need pheromone on this guy.
What's that?
Berserkium?
Very cool.
I hate that I can't kill that guy.
I don't understand what's happening.
I'm gonna go below.
Oh, wow!
Wait, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what?
What did I just destroy?
Oh no, I just destroyed something big.
Something beautiful.
Also, did you notice something?
Wow, Berserkium is on.
Look at this.
It's way more powerful to dig as well.
This is insanity.
It's so good.
That's concentrated mana.
That's right.
You did now.
Berserkium makes your spells insane.
Still won't kill these guys though.
They are incredibly hard to kill.
But somehow he doesn't care about me right now.
That's fine with me.
Now this boss...
Okay, I can't panic this time.
Last time I panicked hard.
When I engaged in that boss fight.
I'm not gonna do that again.
If anything goes to shit, I'm just gonna leave.
And then I come back, you know?
I leave because I have a long distance teleport wand.
Why are they all protected?
Look at how he...
Gravitational feels my thing.
Very annoying.
He's like a tank.
Someone is buffing him for sure.
Is it the bad guy?
No.
It's the mage, I think.
Sometimes their protection falls off for a brief second.
Whoa!
What is going on?
Shit.
Guys, I'm just gonna fuck off.
He has a way too hardcore for me.
Man.
I don't get it.
Everyone has it!
What?
Oh, at least these guys died.
Did I just see them without any for a second there?
That guy.
Gotta catch them when they don't have it on.
Maybe it's like intermittent thing.
Oh, hold on.
Get more blood.
What's up here?
Is that gonna come alive?
That's a lot of concentrated mana.
Got you!
No buff on you, huh?
We have a mage there.
Oh!
Surface!
Look at that!
We can just make our way out like that.
Ah.
What a nice, beautiful day out here, huh?
Well, back to it.
People don't kill themselves, do they?
Kill them?
Oh, this guy's pretty...
Oh, wait.
This is the...
What are you, man?
I have an idea.
Ah, shit.
If I had a tablet, I would try to throw it on him.
I would definitely try that.
It's like the only thing I haven't tried.
That's a pheromone.
You know what?
I kind of want that.
I'm gonna put it on these guys when I see him.
Bye-bye.
He... Okay, he came alive.
Look, they're fighting each other now.
This guy is somehow protected.
By the way, I just realized...
Short-range homing.
I don't think he has a gravitational field.
It's my fucking homing!
That's doing it.
Right?
I'm like 100% sure now.
That's what's happening.
Come on, man.
Die!
They are very resistant to damage, I gotta say.
Aggressive much.
Oh, we're at the surface.
No, wait, we're not.
It looked like we were.
Oh, no.
Hey, actually.
Here.
You are my friend now.
Let's go on adventures together.
Oh, no.
Oh, no!
I got teleported into the boss place.
Oh, no.
Let's just prepare ourselves.
Man, look at all this copper.
Okay, he's here somewhere.
Where are you hiding, sir?
Was this pheromone blood?
Okay.
Oh, no.
There's all kinds of materials here.
I don't trust.
I'm gonna go away from here.
Pheromone is fine to have.
Kill that dude.
Oh, he's protected.
Why are you...
Why are you protected?
Oh, never mind.
He died there.
The alchemists.
I assume there.
That's like the only Finnish word that is like somewhat readable and you understand it when you read it, you know?
Everything else is like...
And it means cat.
Her circum could be cool here.
Oh, is it right here?
Are we just doing it?
Oh, yeah, we are.
Oh, no.
Dude, I'm already so low on HP.
Oh, wait, he does a shield.
I have to be careful here.
Shield is off.
Okay, shield is back on.
Oh, my God.
I'm already losing so much HP.
I'm panicking.
I'm panicking, guys.
No, no, no, no.
We gotta find some blood.
I can't do this.
I have no idea what's happening and I'm gonna die here.
For sure.
Wait, is he following me?
Don't follow me.
I need blood.
Don't not follow me.
There's a lot of blood.
Oh, wait, I need to...
This one.
Good.
No!
Need to be careful here.
I could just go heal with that heart, actually, but isn't that kind of a waste when I have blood?
Drink the blood, drink the blood.
I wouldn't wonder if his health is gonna regenerate.
I don't think I took any of his health, but still.
Just in case.
Oh, this one.
A lot of berserkium here.
Kind of want to grab that.
You know, let's empty Fermone and grab berserkium.
Not there.
Do it up here.
Oh, you know what?
If I could find Ambrosia, that would be really sick.
I'm way too scared.
Okay, this is nice.
This is nice.
Yes.
And we have blood here.
Do you do?
What?
Oh!
I ate too much.
Let's only get blood from now on.
Watch.
Yeah, okay.
You can definitely...
Whoops.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You can definitely grind up their corpses for more blood.
Oh, hello, sir.
Hold on, let me...
Oh, there's actually a bunch of blood there.
Oh, no, he's protected.
Are you standing in Ambrosia or something?
That's whiskey.
They take a bit of damage?
Okay, I don't understand what's happening.
I am so confused.
That's okay.
Give me blood.
What's that?
Mildly boost.
Give me some of this.
Blood me up.
Okay, not bad.
We're getting somewhere.
Maybe we can go back now.
Okay, so let's not panic.
So he does a shield.
He removes the shield intermittently.
And that's what I should shoot.
So I shouldn't do anything.
Only dodge.
Only dodge until shield is down and then we go ahead.
Like, look, I can damage him randomly.
Do we have a wand on him?
Oh, we've got blood.
I'm stuck here.
I'm stuck.
Teleportation.
I should probably wait until I'm not clumsy anymore.
That would make sense.
Ambrosia!
Whoa, but unstable polymorphine in that.
That's not good.
You know what?
I don't care.
I will take a bath.
Come on.
Hey.
Collect some.
I'm just trying to quickly grab some when I'm in between.
Okay, nevermind.
Doesn't seem to work the way I intended.
Oh yeah, look, I'm actually ambrosia'd up right now.
Turn me back.
Am I also confused?
Why is there a question mark on me?
Where's the boss?
Oh, that's unstable polymorphine there.
Oh no.
Where did he go?
Sir?
Where has thou gone?
Show thyself?
Huh?
Did he...
He must have followed me back?
Or something?
Maybe he went this way to follow me.
And then he got lost because I started teleporting all over.
Maybe he's scared of me.
He saw my prowess and decided to run away.
This guy's gone, dude!
All right, let's go hang out in this crib.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, there's stuff up here.
I'm gonna kill these guys.
Kind of relieved the boss is not gonna lie.
Freezing liquid, no thanks.
I don't want that.
Sure as hell do not want teleportation.
Berserkium is actually decent.
Bye-bye.
My plan worked, I think.
Look at this.
I have some ambrosia on me now.
Man.
Oh, there we go.
That's what I'm talking about.
Oh, wait, I'm constantly picking it up.
There we go.
Dammit, it broke.
Got it.
Very neat.
Now, where are you, you motherfucker?
Where art thou?
Huh.
Maybe he really is gone.
That's so weird.
Well, all right.
Dammit!
I wanted to teach him a lesson.
Oh, what's that?
Oh, er.
What's up, people?
You out here digging for gold?
What's going on?
Hemis?
No, those are hortas.
Kind of look like Hemis.
Okay, so the question is, what do I do now?
Hmm.
I guess I can try to go up here again.
I can go to the pyramid.
And actually, there was another place I wanted to check out, which was to the west of here.
I forgot the name of it.
Nope.
Is that the...
essence eater?
The good old essence eater.
Yeah.
Love the digging.
That is an E.
See that?
Beautiful craftsmanship there.
Oh, what's up?
Whoa.
You know what?
Let's just go where the wind takes us.
Like, cool.
Don't know where I am, but this is cool.
Frozen vault.
That's actually exactly what I was looking for.
More of this.
0.47, 0.42, that's a shitty wand.
Also, I need to figure out how to heal with those things.
Maybe I should start experimenting with that, actually.
Hold on.
Let's take it.
Let's take a moment here.
Let's take a quick moment.
Let's see.
What do I have?
How can I make this work?
Reduce lifetime.
Has delay.
Reduce the lifetime of spell.
Remove bounce.
Short range homing.
Hmm.
I don't seem to have anything on me right now that could potentially make this hit me.
You know?
Oh, actually.
I could try to...
Wait.
Oh yeah, it expires after a while.
Right.
Whoops.
What?
Oh, did it shoot the water?
Oh, it shot that one, I think!
Oh my god.
Come on, man.
That's the healing.
Does not come back down.
We need to do something to this.
To make it come back down.
You know what?
It wouldn't be a terrible idea to go through all the holy mountains again, just to see the spells we had.
You know?
Maybe there's a spell there that can assist us.
And we...
Also, we need to go down there anyway to grab the remaining perk.
Yeah.
Let's actually do that.
Seems like a good idea.
What's that?
Frozen blood.
Can I eat that?
And get health?
Is that working?
No.
Unfortunately.
Oh, there's also this thing.
Should I grab that?
I wonder.
Actually, there's something I want to try.
Right here.
So we've got this stuff in here.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
We need to...
Calm down a bit.
Oh, wait, we can't.
Yes, we can.
Never mind.
I hate being out of slots here.
Boink!
Nice.
Uh, okay.
We're gonna try something now.
Let's try all of them.
Let's see what happens.
Actually, they are real letters.
See that?
G, E, D sharp, D.
Ah.
Hmm.
Yeah.
Everybody dance.
This is a cool tune.
Everybody in the world, come on.
Very cool.
Let's swap it around a bit.
A, B, C, D.
Uh.
E, F, G.
Oh, wait.
D sharp, maybe.
Put them in order.
Wait, is that shooting?
Look, it's...
I'm actually hitting the ground with it.
These are projectiles.
That's funny.
What if I were to do this?
What if I shoot music at this?
Okay, whatever.
Uh, nah, let's leave this here for now.
That ain't doing much.
Okay.
Cool.
We will do more experiments later with that.
Actually, let me grab this thing again.
Boink.
And put this one up here.
Cool.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Is this a sequence?
I can't read that.
Nope.
I don't know what that means.
That's sad.
All right.
Well.
Ah, this is where I killed the worm.
That's where I...
Oh my god, look at all this acid in the air.
Flammable gas.
Okay, so the plan is now, we're gonna go through the mountains and find some utility spells that maybe we can use to heal ourselves.
Because we have healing spells, we just don't know how to hit ourselves with them.
It sounds really dumb.
Like, you could just aim the wand at yourself.
Like, you know, like a gun to your head.
Wand to the head, you know?
Why can I not do that?
So we need to do something like that, basically.
I just want to quickly see.
Oh yeah.
I could also try my hand with this guy.
Hmm.
Not yet, not yet.
I'm scared of that guy.
Let's see what we have here.
Oh!
Wait a minute.
I'm gonna take that.
Because maybe that will do something at the egg place.
What should I replace?
Maybe this one.
Put it there.
You know what?
Let's have it in here for now.
That's fine.
What's this?
Blood cloud!
Yo, that's actually big!
Right?
Dude.
I have an idea.
We're gonna be healing.
This is our heal!
Also, wait a minute.
Electric torch.
Sea of acid.
I don't want sea of acid.
Let's find a good place for this.
I need to find a big pool, basically.
Or I can store some blood.
Like a reservoir, you know?
I mean, I guess that will do what I just found there.
We can probably make it even better.
Oh, I've been here already.
I dug here!
Cool.
Actually kind of a small level when you think about it.
When you have this much freedom and movement, everything seems much smaller, right?
I wanted to explore the rest of this place anyway.
Maybe there's a heart I missed.
What is it with these?
I kind of want to empty them all.
But I actually need another bottle.
Maybe I'll get rid of berserkium for now.
I can drink it.
Drink that shit.
We have some blood.
Cool.
Very cool.
Look at the digging when you have berserkium.
Cool.
It's absolutely unhinged.
Wait, does that...
Oh, okay.
Maybe it will let me go through denser stuff.
When I have berserkium.
Not the case, it seems.
Jesus Christ.
Oh!
Right.
I'm immune.
Everything is fine.
What's up, fools?
What do we got here?
Oh, this place!
I've come for revenge!
Hey, you know what?
I'll take one of these.
Thanks.
In fact, hold on.
I take multiple of these.
Let me see how good this is.
Where's it?
There.
Isn't there one more?
Is that better?
I'm actually not sure.
Let's try it for a bit.
Also, my spells are left behind.
That's kind of scary right now.
Wow.
No, thanks.
What is that?
We're in pheromone.
Also, let's get this blood.
Oh, no.
My spells are here.
Spells are there.
We're fine.
Throw that away.
The thing I'm scared of in this place is actually polymorphine, because there's always so much of it here.
Oh, no.
Slime potion?
Wait, did I actually appear right where I left off?
That's insane chance.
Well, almost the same place.
I think these are better, by the way.
But this way, we have a bit of everything.
This way, we don't have the knockback.
That's something.
Or the recoil.
What do you have there?
Nothing interesting.
Concentrate a mana?
The fuck is that?
Copy random spell thrice.
I don't like that.
I don't like randomness.
Randomness bad.
Also, it's my thing.
I feel like I'm not doing as much damage anymore.
What's that?
Concentrated mana.
That's fine.
Dude, I'm murdering this place, and it feels incredible.
Oh, no.
Wait, wait.
I have to remember Ambrosia is...
Oh, shit.
I need to be careful there.
Acid potion.
No, thanks.
Although, you know what?
Yes.
I just want another potion.
You like acid, sir?
This is for you.
Notice how it instantly evaporates.
That's kind of interesting.
I wonder what that is.
No, I'm slimy.
Something exploded here.
Wait a minute.
We've seen this one before, but hold on.
What are you shooting?
Oh, no.
Okay, we don't have it on us anymore.
We're back here now.
Man, those teleporting guys are so scary.
No, thanks.
Where was I?
Somewhere over here.
Is that...
That is teleportation right there.
It's everywhere.
Ah, okay.
I was standing on it.
I see.
How do we get rid of it?
Let's take a channel.
Hopefully, I can't destroy the book.
Let's see.
One of my brethren ran away in order to escape our predicament.
They felt our understanding of this world was to be forbidden.
They hit something here in this room, but...
I lack the ability to truly see what is here.
Fuck!
I need worm blood.
To truly see what is here.
In this room?
Unless it's not talking about the room where this book is right now, but somewhere else.
One of my brethren ran away in order to escape our predicament.
Okay.
Oh!
Spark bolts are here.
I'm so confused why this one was shooting spark bolts.
I understand now.
But I guess...
Is that okay if I do that?
Wait a minute.
What?
Sorry, I had a sneeze there.
Okay.
Uh, I don't think I like this.
Put it away.
We'll just rock with the one of these.
It's fine.
And now we can do this.
We're back in action.
Except, you know what's crazy?
I still haven't found a goddamn plasma cutter.
That blows my mind.
Invicebleum.
You know what?
I will take it.
Thanks.
Seems pretty cool to have.
Like right now, actually.
Oh wait, you don't drink it.
You throw it on yourself.
Fuck off.
Damn it.
I hit the teleportation.
Didn't mean to.
That's invicebleum.
Man, this place is kind of small.
Is it not?
I feel like this is really small.
Yeah.
Like mega small.
What is that?
Oh, it's honey.
Destroy it.
We don't want honey in this world.
We haven't been down here.
Worm pheromone and...
Just a potion?
What?
Whoop.
I broke the worm pheromone.
I want blood.
Wand?
I can get there.
I have a black hole.
Let me do it.
I gotta be careful here.
Put these here for now.
Shit!
I didn't mean to do that.
It was muscle memory.
Got to change it back.
What do we got?
Oh, nice.
I'll take that.
You can't get enough of these, right?
Or maybe you can't get enough.
That's up for debate, I guess.
I feel like in this case, I'm actually running out of spells.
Slots.
Gotta get that blood.
Sweet.
And I have not overeaten, but I am worm food right now.
Nice.
I also have to remember I have that spell.
That feels like an emergency thing.
Man, this place is nothing.
Ah!
A wand for the me.
Interesting.
This one is an egg.
The other one was a hollow egg.
Maybe I'll take this one with me as well.
For science.
You know what?
Let's get rid of this one, liquid vacuum field.
I feel like... no.
I've been carrying that around forever.
You know?
And I don't want to carry it anymore.
Am I actually digging slower than usual?
What is that?
That's oil.
I may as well get more gold right in case I need to reroll once more.
You never know.
Digging.
Wait, why did I take damage?
Like I vote two, maybe.
And I need a spell that will allow me to heal myself, you know, with the healing spell.
Aha!
That's water.
Whoa, I'm burning.
In fact, fill it up.
Oh wait, is it water though?
Last time it wasn't water, it was something else and I've never figured it out.
Hmm.
Fuck me.
Once again, there's a triangle on it.
Actually, there is a cloud.
Steam?
Water into steam?
Water?
Make it a cloud?
How do I do that?
Oops.
Oh, I ran out of water because I just used it all.
Fuck me.
Oh wait.
Hey, that works.
Ambrosia to the rescue.
Gold, gold, gold.
Gimme, gimme, gimme.
Gimme water.
Actually, there's way more water somewhere.
Hold on, how do I even do this?
I need fire then.
I don't even know, I'm unsure about that anyway.
I don't think it's cloud.
Let me go right side.
Did I even explore all of this?
Here we go.
Let's try water.
If it's not water, we can try something else.
And the thing is, honestly, I don't want to try too much anyway with this thing because like, it's gonna contain like, something pretty shitty anyway, right?
Like, this is the coal pits.
It's not really gonna blow my mind, I think.
Whatever reward we may get.
Now I don't even know where it was.
I'm actually really lost.
Oh, oh wait.
I went here, I think.
Did I check this?
I did.
So I went this way and then I went here.
Ah, here we are.
Fill it up and give me rewards.
Doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo.
I mean, if we get lava in there somehow, that will do it.
No, that will just produce rock, no?
Nah.
Whatever.
Let's continue.
Let's see what we have here.
It's so dark here for some reason.
Oh, it's...
Yeah, I remember now.
It was dark here because it's dark here.
That's the answer to that.
I definitely did not go in there, I don't think.
Cluster bolt.
That is not gonna assist in the healing.
What's going on there?
The fuck?
Okay, he woke up.
Not that it matters, he's just gonna die.
I think the thing is, it's so dark here, you don't actually know where you've been or not.
I sort of remember this.
But over here...
Like, you can't tell because it won't show light where you've been.
Okay, now we're at the edge.
Ah, and this is gonna lead up to...
Yeah, this is gonna lead up to the hemisphere.
Beautiful.
Oh, I left that there.
Oh, that's fun.
A bunch of those as well.
Dynamite.
What do we got?
Water trail.
Plasma beam bounce.
Nope.
No thanks.
Oh, I remember this one.
Dang, it's been a while, huh?
And now we're at the bottom.
Look at that now.
Prickly sp...
teleport bolt.
Oh, that's the shitty version, I don't want that.
Although, this is actually a pretty good wand.
Imagine finding this back then here.
That would have been sick.
Good spells, good wand itself as well.
Very solid.
Levitation.
Dude, I feel like a god in this game right now.
Oh, what's up, guys?
Uh, that's also a pretty sick wand, I guess, for the time.
What do we got here, though?
Accelerative homing.
Spark bolts.
A lot of them.
Nah, I can do without.
I'm okay.
Whoa, that's a lot of freezing vapor.
Shit!
Wow, that's that?
That is that, boys!
That's brutal.
Wait, why is total death 72?
That's not right.
Wait.
That should be 74 now.
I think that's bugged.
I have 74 deaths, not 72.
That is bugged.
Wow.
Well, that was a sick run.
A bit unfortunate, though.
So, have it end that way.
It is what it is, though.
Rip.
We go again.
Maybe this time, we can actually get to fight the Alchemist guy.
Whoops!
I was in teleport wand mode already.
It's... Number two is not teleport right now.
It's a bomb.
This is gonna be so hard to get rid of, muscle memory-wise.
Oh, already there's electricity here.
That's bad.
Shit.
This is what killed me last time!
You know what's funny?
I couldn't get out at all, because I was stunned.
And before I could...
Before the stun ran out, I got shocked again.
And it just kept going.
Like, you're dead.
If that happens.
Oh, thanks.
Black hole for me.
That's actually pretty dope.
A black hole this early?
That makes me feel special.
Who's hiding over here?
So, toxic sludge.
I wonder if there's something about this, you know?
Like, what if I drain it?
Can I even...
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I mean, that's not gonna drain, of course, because there's metal at the bottom.
There's a wand there, though.
No, go around.
Do not waste bombs.
Don't be really dumb.
Ultra safe, kill him long distance.
Hey!
Dude, I'm getting some sick digging wands here.
What the hell?
And also, it's a pretty decent wand in itself.
Like, it's not bad.
What's up here?
Nothing.
Oh, you know what?
I'm gonna grab this tablet.
This is actually a deadly weapon.
A highly deadly weapon in the hands of a skilled craftsman.
I gotta go around.
Doop, doop, doop, doop, doop, doop, doop, doop, doop, doop.
Watch this.
Like, 26 damage in the beginning of the game is a lot.
Just wait for them to cross the corner, and then you fuck them.
Wait.
Maybe the Horda's way can kill normal.
You don't need that kind of thing here.
Uh-oh.
I didn't mean to destroy that fucking flask.
That's annoying.
This guy's shotgunning.
I was just about to eat the blood, but of course I can't do that.
Uh, torch.
You know what, actually?
I have an idea.
A torch.
Does that...
If I get to the cave, I want to see if that actually lights it up.
Maybe I'm too fucking logical here, but having a torch in a cave, unheard of, right?
But probably it ain't gonna work.
But I'm gonna try it nonetheless.
Hey.
Getting that worm blood is one hell of an annoying thing to do.
Also, I've only ever seen the torch spell in this level, I think.
Okay, give me that.
Actually doing pretty well on money so far.
Um...
I'm gonna go around.
Uh-oh.
There we go.
Despatched.
I think I'm getting better at dodging.
Like, just in general.
Simple shots like that.
Way better at it now.
Even compared to just last run at the beginning.
I got a lot of combat practice.
Whoa!
Didn't make it.
Let's check this out.
Hymnus.
Thank God I haven't discovered any of the fire dudes yet.
This looks weirdly half circular.
Doesn't it?
Wait a sec.
I mean, there was blood in here to begin with.
Maybe we needed to put that in there.
Acceleration was there.
Oh wait, is that bottle still there?
Wait, no way.
The bottle is still working!
I thought that was broken.
Yo, that's big.
Thanks.
Very nice.
You there.
Oh, I'm not gonna go.
Am I gonna go through here?
Yes, I am.
We can mix it.
That's fine.
Look at them having a bath.
It's a communal bath.
Hey.
Guys.
There we go.
So much water here.
More acceleration.
I'm gonna accelerate so much.
May as well accelerate right now.
Fast as fuck, boy.
Flammoxium, no thanks.
I do wonder though, if you put that on enemies, maybe they're gonna be like completely flammoxed by it.
I mean, like, maybe they won't attack you at all.
They're just gonna go around in a haze, you know?
We should try that.
Just to see.
Gunpowder.
Oh, I wanna blow that up.
Wap!
There we go.
Easy peasy.
And a slime ball.
Nah.
Not feeling the slime ball.
I wanna go through these walls with the teleporter.
You see this?
That collection of explosives we've seen before.
That is 100% like a map tile or something.
I was just about to use the teleport one that I don't have again.
Good thing I'm out of...
Oh, it's a torch there now.
Right.
Actually, this is a really weird spell, isn't it?
If you think about it, it's a passive-type spell.
We have...
Is that the only passive-type spell?
I have not seen that anywhere else.
You can't shoot it.
You can't really...
You can just sort of hold it.
Very odd.
That is a potion.
A circium!
Ooh!
Yeah, let's get rid of this.
Nobody wants that anyway.
A berserkium!
Yes!
No health!
Sometimes there's a health below these things.
Am I kind of stuck?
Do I need to blow my way out or...
I mean, I can.
I have the means.
I even have the holes.
That are black.
Okay, we seem to be fine.
And go around.
What's that say?
Gunpowder!
It's a pouch!
More acceleration.
Wow.
Sweet!
Oh my god, I keep getting better and better potions!
Let's get rid of acceleration.
No!
You bastard!
Pick up what we can.
Breaking mind is a fucking emceebeleum potion.
Meow, meow.
I'm speedrunning, look at this.
Collapsed mines time.
Oh god.
It smells like soil after rain?
Is that this?
It's gotta be.
Okay.
Get rid of that shit.
Soil after rain, huh?
I personally am a favorite of the concrete after rain.
Or the sidewalk after rain.
Love that smell.
Sometimes I just go out there and I put my nose right down next to it and I go...
And I go, oh yeah.
Such a smell.
The best of smells.
You there.
Look how speedrunny I am.
This guy!
I don't like that guy.
So we blow him up.
That's what we do to people we don't like, we just blow him up.
Boink.
That was a perfect shot!
Wow!
I'm proud of myself.
Polymorphine, no thanks.
That's for you.
There we go.
Cleaning up the streets.
Don't fall into it!
Oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no.
Water me, water me.
Nice.
Oh, let's try this here.
It actually works!
Wait, it even works...
What?
Wow, okay, it even works on the water.
Look at this!
Acceleration, baby!
Coming in clutch!
Wait, where am I?
Uh-oh.
Wait, I don't want to go that way.
No, no, no.
No way, Jose.
Aha!
Yes!
Wait, we need to like...
I ran out of...
Oh no.
Guys.
No, we're not stuck, we're not stuck.
We're stuck.
That was scary.
God damn.
I didn't fear for a moment, though.
I had it all along.
I was merely faking, being nervous.
Not real.
Nope.
Ah!
Hello.
There's a chest.
There's a guy again.
Sir Guy?
Uh-oh.
Okay.
We have a problem.
How am I gonna do this?
Oh, I have an idea, I have an idea.
Watch this.
This is so smart.
Hehehehe.
Hehehe!
Fuck you!
I'm a genius.
Gimme that.
Water for me.
Um...
Sawblade orbit!
Holy shit!
That is kinda nuts.
I think I like it.
Thanks!
Pretty cool.
Hey, look!
Ah!
Sawblades.
Sawblades, guys.
They're dangerous, okay?
What the fuck is this guy doing here?
That's what I wanna know.
Hahahaha!
Damn it, man!
That was such a good start, though!
That was such a good start!
Shit!
That was fun, actually.
You know, this game always has a way...
Also, I have acid here.
Let's just mentally make a note of that.
The game always has a way of...
I don't know.
Just showing you what's what, you know?
When you get to...
What do you call it?
When there's too much hubris.
That's when the game strikes.
Or when things are going just a bit too well.
Then the engine of this game is like...
Power detected.
Tone it down a bit.
You know, and they're gonna fuck me.
One more.
No!
Oh, wait.
I have more.
Wow, this one sucks.
Beautiful.
In fact, I'll take this one, too!
Come here.
You're a deadly weapon.
Deadly weapon.
Yoink.
And now everything shakes again and an evil roar in the distance.
The mines.
The hemisphere.
That's a trap.
But you know what?
I can outrun it.
Easy.
No problem.
That guy, though.
He... how about a bit of that?
And some of that.
That's what I'm talking about.
There we go!
Pretty neat.
I'll take that.
In fact, I should have thrown the tablet on him.
Why didn't I think?
The tablet method.
The tabloid.
I should have given him a column.
Whoop.
Oh, he died.
You know why he died?
Because I have the best starter spell right now.
The energy orb.
It's unbeatable.
Hey, sir.
It's for you!
Okay, never mind.
Oh, let's grab that first.
What's that?
That was inviscibilium.
Very cool.
Dude!
Oh, the ultimate combo.
Watch this.
Hello.
That's fucking awesome!
Oh, that's...
I just imagined someone actually invisible.
Running around with a huge object and just going bloop!
The mental image on that is hilarious.
Holy crap.
Oh, I love this game, man.
It's too good.
You there!
Watch this.
Oh, he didn't die from it!
All right.
Oh wait, where's my tablet?
I was about to throw a tablet at him and then I forgot where...
There it is.
I was so excited that I forgot to bring it.
Excitement took over there.
It's okay.
I remember that's all that matters.
Thank you.
There's oil in that box.
Oh!
Sometimes they stack and it's hard to know.
I should have seen that coming.
It's okay, though.
I didn't lose that much HP.
Things are still a-okay.
Man, what was up with the guy who killed us last run, man?
In the first level, someone like that was sawblade orbit or like sawblade spells?
What the fuck is going on?
Can't believe there's a spell refresher in that chest.
Unstable.
No.
You know, in the beginning of the game, I was very taken with the teleportation stuff.
I loved having it.
Like, especially unstable because that would allow me to go explore random places.
Actually, I will take it.
Better than as it.
Don't like as it.
Oh wait, that's not water.
Thought I had water on me.
I
didn't look at him.
He's hiding under the table.
Come out.
Thanks.
Give me some hearts.
Would love that.
I have a feeling.
I thought maybe that would be a hard in there.
I'm kind of stuck now.
I'm going to be lazy.
Oh, man.
Oh, that was not worth it at all.
Jesus!
What's going on here?
Is that all oil?
Wow.
Insano style.
Can I get?
Yeah, hold on.
I actually kind of forgot I had that spell.
Let me go up here.
What's crack-a-lacking?
Blow everything up.
I think I already checked that one.
I've not been here, though.
Hmm.
I have a feeling.
You know what?
I should stop listening to those feelings I have.
Those feelings are not good feelings.
The collapsed mines.
There's a wand.
Look at all the hammers.
What's up, everybody?
Whoops.
Uh-oh.
I am s- Oh.
I guess I must have hit some teleportation.
Wait, what was I?
Dude, I'm so scared of electricity now.
I have like a new fear.
Oh, it's right there.
I...
Man.
If I see electricity immunity in the future, I think I may just take it.
Just because of that experience I just had.
I'm scarred forever.
I- I've been hurt.
I'm not okay.
I'm not.
Especially that fucking thing.
Just sitting there emitting electricity in the water, waiting.
In the most unlikely of places, too.
You know?
Where you- When you least expect it.
Wow.
I may just go through.
Nah, hold on.
There's a little tiny bit to explore.
I could get lucky.
Nope.
What?
Oh, I get it.
Oh my god, I thought I sprue water.
Oh no.
Oh no, water.
I understand.
I was fucking- Unstable teleportation.
I mistook it for water.
A classic.
That's the tree.
Ah, we're here now.
I wonder if this will let me see in there Fireball.
It's fire, right?
Just like a torch.
Logic would say that that wouldn't work.
Let's try it.
Wait, how do I get in?
Does this even destroy roots?
Wow, did you hear that?
When it bounced off of the wood, it sounded like metal.
Is the tree made of metal?
Hold on, does this?
What?
I don't- I have no idea how that just worked, but sure.
Drain it!
And
then...
Let's see now.
I mean, it does produce a flash, but it will not allow me to see.
What about...
Ah!
We're leaving.
Yikes, that hurt.
Let me throw away this shit.
Wait, isn't that just gonna come back down?
Fuck.
Eh, hold on.
We need that water before we go.
Very important.
Let's throw it down here.
What if I drink it?
Oh, just drink it all.
I don't care.
Yeah, teleport me, I don't care.
Do it, do it, do it.
This is also an experiment anyway.
What are the limits of this unstable teleportation?
You know?
Nice.
Okay, that went pretty good.
Let's go.
Can we heal up?
Is that a wand right down there?
It is, look at that.
Cool.
Nice.
Okay.
Meh.
Nice.
Uh...
Yike.
We're back, baby.
Fuck yeah.
I will buy this.
I will buy...
No.
I have no more money.
Whoops.
But I will buy this.
That's fine.
Okay.
Uh, let's see.
We have energy sphere.
We have this wand, which actually not bad.
That is an okay wand, I would say.
Let's energy sphere the shit out of this.
And do something like that.
How about them apples?
Hey!
Already!
Look at me, I'm a pro.
I know how to build these wands, man.
But it's not actually amazing.
Because, you know, it uses it up so fast.
Is it actually better to just...
Nah, I like that.
What if we go nuts?
All right, let's not go that nuts.
But it's fun.
Very cool.
What does this do at the end?
Right.
What if I do this?
Okay.
What if I remove that?
All right.
I think we're...
Oh, hold on.
This costs five mana?
Cost...
Now we're talking!
Dope shit right there.
It's a short lift, but it's fine.
That's a lot of damage for right now.
Okay, then I also need to get this one when I have the money.
Yeah, let's put this one on that.
Let's see here.
What if we do this?
What if we actually just chainsaw?
Oh, it's gonna shoot three of them at the same time there.
That's pretty dope.
In fact, this shoots four.
Nah, no, no, no.
That's bad.
Put it back up here.
Point two seven, point two...
Nah, that one sucks.
Oh!
Wait a minute, though.
That's kind of bad because of the mana recharge.
That sucks.
Yeah, this is good for now.
We have a bit of digging there.
I'm gonna grab the remaining bombs that I have.
Put them up here.
Oh, they're actually empty.
Wait, is this a good wand?
No, this is a shuffle wand.
What about that one?
Shuffle.
Oh, but actually...
No.
Nope.
Bag of ghosts.
All right, let's go.
This is a sick wand, actually.
Very dope.
Oh, wait, should I...
There's no way.
I need to just go.
I was trying to see if I could get out of the holy mountain without angering.
But the only way to do that is to have a long-distance cast.
Getting a little too comfortable already.
Need to calm myself.
Bro!
What a shot.
I gotta commend them for that.
That was beautiful.
But the good news is, we can drink blood and we now have the power of the potion bottle.
Nothing can stop us now.
Except electricity and fire.
Explosions.
The gods.
A lot of things.
Whoa, I think I take that.
Thanks.
Fireball orbit, huh?
Not bad at all.
Drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink.
In fact, I may just replace this concentrated mana with...
This is gonna be my blood potion.
And then we have the tablet.
We can throw at people.
Does this dig?
Oh my god, it does!
Oh, but it's shitty mana, so it's not actually that worth.
But if the mana is close to the surface, I take it.
Like here.
Yeah, sort of.
It's not the best.
It feels, it's really fun to shoot, I have to say that.
This one is really fun.
Just the sound of it makes me happy.
What was that?
Oh, a biggie.
Nice.
Oh, my dude has a wand.
And that's kind of a cool wand.
Thank you.
Look at that, it shoots in two directions too.
A little bit weird to shoot.
Ow!
Dripping fucking acid on me.
We gotta get some blood in our system here.
Hey, come here.
Blood, blood, blood.
Whoa!
Where's your mom?
How did that hit me?
I'm way too careless.
Okay, there should be blood down here now.
I killed a bot.
Yeah, here we go, here we go.
So, I'm gonna empty this.
What is this one again?
Concentrate, I can't drink that, right?
Yeah, I can.
Yes, I can.
That's actually amazing.
Dude!
Oh, concentrated mana is sick.
That is actually wild.
Like, in the right situation, that can be really good.
Hold on, let me...
Look at that, I produced some blood.
Is that a...
Hold on, check this out, this is meat.
I shoot it.
Blood comes out.
It does not dig through wood.
Or gunpowder.
You know what?
I could be lucky.
Sometimes, these portals are filled with blood.
So, if I check out every portal, maybe I get lucky.
And see one filled with blood.
Maybe this one, you know?
Let's bomb it.
Why is that dynamite so weak?
Okay, so this one is not the one.
Oh, wait, I can't get up here.
Actually, I can.
Especially with concentrated mana.
Oh, you need to...
Okay, you know what I just noticed?
It only digs very close quarters.
Like, look at this.
Does nothing.
That works.
Isn't that interesting?
There's a proximity effect there.
Wait a minute, unless...
Unless the chainsaw is actually what's doing the digging, I just realized.
Am I being dumb here?
Personal makes creatures hit by a projectile gain a temporary gravity well that draws projectiles in.
Yeah, you know what?
Yes, that sounds like fun.
Let's do a bit of that.
Kill him.
Stop pooping, babies!
I bet, dude, there's something in there.
Let's see if I'm right.
I can't get in there, can I?
I can.
Nevermind.
I thought there may have been something in there.
I've won, though.
Why am I?
Oh, I'm poisoned.
Oh, we ran out of concentrated mana, that sucks.
No, I'm gonna get in there.
There's no way I'm not gonna get in there.
Or
maybe I'm not getting in there.
I don't have anything else.
Nah, this is gonna work for sure.
Nice!
Whoa!
Damn!
That wand is sweet!
I will, I think I'll take that.
Maybe even replace this one.
That's pretty dope.
Still no blood down here.
Killed himself.
Get back through the tunnel.
That sludge.
The mixing is insane!
The mixer!
Nice.
That makes me feel better now about doing that.
Thanks.
Just a bit of money in the pocket.
Something in there.
I see you.
Not very interesting.
Let's go.
Should be a bit more to explore over here.
And of course, there's also the fungal caverns.
But I'm not gonna go there.
That shit is crazy.
It's over here.
Nothing.
Oh no, I don't want to get in there.
I think it's time to leave.
Let's go.
We heal?
Is that long this...
Wait, teleporting cast.
Uh, hold on.
I'm not quite sure what that is.
But look at that.
Yoink!
No more fire, baby!
This one is sweet.
I want reduced red for sure.
Ooh, short range homing.
What is this one?
Cast a spell from the closest enemy.
Uh...
Oh!
Huh?
Wait.
I have ideas.
Cast a spell from it, right?
Huh?
Why...
Why didn't it shoot it here?
That's the closest enemy.
You bastard.
Fucking liar.
Giant magic missile.
The most powerful version of magic missile.
Yeah, holy damn.
120... you know what?
This would not be a bad idea just to have...
on one of the wands.
For one of those oh shit moments, and you need to kill something immediately.
You know?
I dig it.
Saw blades though?
I don't think I dig it.
It's one of those things that make me go heh heh.
When I see them, you know?
Like my vision would go like this.
Looking at the TNT here and then...
Heh.
And then it keeps going.
It's always like that.
Glowing lands.
No, this one for sure.
Homing for sure.
Glowing lands.
And maybe light.
No, I have 100 money left.
What's that?
Oh, the late spell cast.
Light.
No.
I think that's it for now.
I have done my shopping.
Also, we have light already.
I was almost about to buy it.
What an idiot choice that would be.
Uh, no, actually, you know what?
Maybe I wanna keep that one.
That could be cool somehow, right?
Flamethrower.
Wait, explosive damage?
Huh?
Ah!
That would be a way to make steam, I...
Hold on.
Is it?
Let's test.
Yeah?
Yeah, that makes steam.
In case we ever need it.
Clouds are basically that.
Um, chain...
Excuse me.
I'm gonna need some Admana, in fact.
That's right.
That's like my issue here.
Also, hold on.
160, 50.
That wand right there is nuts.
Hold on.
Look at this.
Look at that!
Infinite shooting right there.
What if we had this?
Do we even need this?
Oh yeah.
Wait.
Hold on.
Hold the fuck on!
Oh, yeah, we do.
Wait.
This makes no sense.
Hold on.
So notice how the recharge timer does not start.
You see that?
So that means we're limited by castelay.
But that doesn't make any sense.
Oh, this one.
That doesn't make any sense.
Because look at the castelay, it's 0.03.
And that one is 0.33, so in total we have 0.36, right?
This one only removes recharge.
In fact, it removes exactly the amount that's on this wand.
Look at that.
The recharge time is zero right now.
That's why we don't see a recharge.
Why is this not limited by castelay?
Why is the castelay not 0.36?
That's the real question.
Wait a minute.
So look now, recharge.
And that makes sense, because...
No, wait a minute, actually.
Hold on.
The recharge is still firing right now.
Hmm.
That's interesting.
What if I do this?
It actually does nothing?
But it's...
Okay, maybe I don't understand chainsaw after all, guys.
I thought I finally understood it.
That fucking spell is driving me nuts.
I swear to God.
Whatever.
Whatever, it works.
Oh, wow.
Oh, 25?
Oh, I see why that's so expensive, then.
But hold on.
This is eight damage.
That is... solid as hell.
If...
Oh, I need to increase lifetime of this somehow.
That would be dope.
I do kind of like the glowing lands spam.
Blowing lands spam is cool.
Hold on, reduce spread.
There's a bit of spread on that, isn't there?
Not much, but it's there.
Hey!
Sweet!
Very cool.
And...
Now I just need speed up.
That would be fantastic on this.
Or homing!
But wait, homing costs a lot of mana.
Yeah, fuck that, fuck that.
That costs too much mana.
Way too much mana.
I like that, I think.
And then we can have...
something like this.
Why is there so much spread on it?
Because it adds spread!
See, that makes sense.
This does 25 damage.
That's actually solid.
So if we do like this...
And...
Actually, no, we don't even need that.
Because it spells per cast seven.
Damn.
This one, though.
Hold on, it costs 80 mana.
Yeah, that's not good.
That's not good.
It costs 30 mana, 80 mana.
Huh.
I don't know if I want this.
Hold on, how far does that go?
It goes a decent distance, actually, compared to this.
You know?
I think that's worth it.
Let's go with that.
That seems cool.
This is a good wand.
Do we even need this?
I... yeah, I guess a little bit.
But...
Hold on.
Reduce.
Wait!
If we do this...
I...
Oh, we can test that, hold on.
So it shoots chainsaw.
And then it shoots chainsaw and...
Oh wait, ran out of mana?
Hold on.
It shoots that one.
If we do this...
Oh, okay.
It is actually using this again.
But it's being applied to the chainsaw only.
Which is kind of useless.
And actually, this is bad...
This is bad for us, because this costs an extra mana then, I guess.
This is one mana less expensive.
But if this was an add mana, you would put it here.
Right?
Get the double effect from that.
Okay.
I would love the teleport, but I don't...
Oh, wait a minute.
I'm an idiot.
Why didn't I go back to grab the teleport from the other holy mountain?
No!
What am I doing?
Okay, that sucks.
That's not bad.
Honestly, I like it.
I like that.
Maybe put this on it, huh?
Hey?
Hey!
But maybe put it here.
Just because mana.
Yes!
That's...
Oh wait, this shuffle.
Maybe that one.
I mean, it's not really that great.
Honestly, the first one we have is so much better.
Yeah, fuck these two ones.
They suck!
Actually, no, nevermind.
This one always casts something.
What was that?
Grab... oh yeah.
Oh, look at this!
Always casts, but it's a limited one.
So it does not always cast.
It always casts the next 20 times.
After you cast it, after that it never casts.
All right, whatever.
I'm leaving.
Actually, am I?
What about this fire and brimstone thingy?
Explosion of brimstone.
Seven damage.
Ten mana drain.
Fiery explosion.
That could be combined with that, maybe?
Let's try it.
Please don't shoot it at me.
I'm probably gonna take damage here.
What?
Oh!
Wait, what?
Yeah, that's not good.
I think it worked on this one over here because I was closer.
And then when I wasn't closer, it prioritized me, which is weird.
All right.
Well, cool.
Let's go.
Let's suck all!
Get the water.
The snowy depths.
We have arrived.
And already taking a bunch of damage.
No, wait.
I took a bunch of damage up in the Holy Mountain.
Also, there's a wand over here somewhere.
No, was that the last one I think?
I think it was the last one.
Shit.
Whoa!
What's up, my dude?
Would you like some...
Oh, watch this.
No, no, no, no, no,
no.
That was a bit too close.
I didn't quite realize where he was until the last moment.
Does this dig?
Not really.
Decent.
I'm a fan.
That does not dig at all.
Had to sneeze.
Someone's throwing those things with a wand.
Sir, come here.
Where are you?
Dumbass.
Whoa!
What an explosion!
Here comes the gang.
Oh, wow.
We're dying.
Jesus.
Okay, we gotta eat.
Can I make...
Make blood.
Look at this!
Whoops.
Get the blood.
Yes, drink.
Too bad it all fell down here.
Actually, not too bad.
I love this.
No, no, no.
Don't put acid in there.
You're gonna ruin it!
Fuck you!
You motherfucker.
It was pure and clean and nice blood.
Until this fool came along.
Look how fast we heal in the beginning, because we don't have that much HP.
This is big.
Dude, vampirism.
So good.
I'm eating the snow, it seems.
Hopefully, nobody peed in it.
No!
Thank God we have some DPS.
There we go.
Make blood.
Look at that.
Wait, what just happened?
Oh, we're full.
I'm just not used to healing that fast with blood, so I was just consuming, consuming, consuming.
We can actually dig with this.
Oh, no, we can't.
It's the chainsaw again.
Why do I bamboozle myself all the time?
In fact, is the chainsaw the one cutting up these corpses?
That makes a lot of sense.
Actually, because it doesn't work at a distance.
Broken wand for me!
All right, fuck off.
You come with me.
That's a rock.
10 damage, 20 mana drain.
Interesting.
Yes.
That went a lot better than I expected just now.
Oh,
this is hell.
Hold on.
Oh, we need a proper digging wand.
Wow, that took a lot of my HP.
A rat came out of nowhere.
What is that?
Upwards, Lord.
Why is this so expensive on the mana?
Is it that good?
I don't understand.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
It is good.
Healing?
Deadly heal on this?
You shoot it below you?
It goes up.
Who does it hit?
You.
Bubble spark.
Wait, bubble spark is...
No, I hate bubble spark.
Yeah, I hate that.
But I'm just getting ideas for like...
I need to just generally keep an eye out for spells that could work in combination with deadly heal.
If I were to find it again.
Did that guy just kill himself?
That was beautiful.
Well done, sir.
Also, I killed him.
You gonna wake up?
A sniper.
No match for me, though.
Another electric charge with firebomb.
I think firebomb could be pretty sick if you have a speed up on it.
You know?
Like these shoot really slow, but if you can make them go fast, I think that would really kick some ass.
I'll take it.
That's a Kiva skeevy.
Oh, that's right.
I'm immune to fire.
I forgot about that.
So watch this.
Nothing happens now.
But if I go close, blood chainsaw.
I'm cutting up the corpse.
You know what's funny, actually?
The game basically told me about this from the very first moment I entered the game.
If you remember, we saw one of the shotgun people chop up his friend and blood came out.
Remember that?
I can't believe it's been in front of our eyes this whole time.
Okay, I may just go.
Hmm, should I really keep going here?
Ouch.
I mean, I can drink blood.
I can keep going.
Yeah, I'm not done here.
No way, Jose.
Oh my god, the digging is atrocious.
Wow.
Angry.
Ah, wand.
Hello.
But only two slots?
I don't know about that.
It is kind of dope, though.
This is actually kind of dope.
Two slots.
What can I do with two slots?
I can probably do...
This would probably be pretty good with a glowing lance.
Point three.
Yeah, I'll take it.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Let's not just accidentally die here.
Oh, I have full blood.
Nice.
Look at that!
Almost full HP again!
Vampire is sick!
Especially early on.
Wow.
And when does this matter the most?
Like, when do you die the most early on, right?
It is absolutely ins...
Okay, watch this.
Yeah, blood.
Blood for me.
Vampire is basically...
You get infinite exploration.
Oh yeah, let's go in here.
Hold on, can we...
I need to start putting light on my shit whenever I go into snowy depths.
Because there's this place here, always.
You know?
I didn't think...
I even have a light.
Like, it wouldn't have cost me anything to put this on.
Except one mana.
I'm willing to pay one mana.
But I'm not a pussy I'm going in anyway.
This place shall be explored.
Especially because there's health.
Or a heart, I should say.
Why is it question marks?
That's what I wonder.
Do I even have a means of getting in there?
I don't.
So what am I even doing here?
I guess getting the heart is what I'm doing here.
Oh.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
It is mine.
Nice.
Wait, is that a- Whoa.
Wow.
Dude, this one has some DPS already.
Let's say this one does not fuck around.
Like, I'm not kidding.
This is some serious business.
For some reason, it doesn't do anything against that.
Oh, never mind.
Wait, is he immune to this shit?
He's not, okay.
I guess he just has a bunch of HP.
Interesting.
Damn it, I want teleport wand through walls.
I have become addicted.
I need it.
So bad.
Who is this?
Show yourself.
It's you!
Should we keep clearing?
It's a good amount of money you get in here, actually.
I think it's worth it.
I was gonna move on from after this anyway, so let's just grab a bit of money and get out.
Ouch.
That's a danger spell.
Very hard to dodge.
Whoa!
Okay, okay.
What the fuck was I hitting?
Faith.
Oh.
Right, that makes a lot of sense.
Come on, get rid of it!
Where are you?
My turn.
Look at that sweet money.
And now I hit home.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Watch this.
Yes.
It's so violent.
Huh?
What does that affect on me?
Oh, ambiguous meat.
Oh, oh, that's not good.
Ambiguous meat is very bad.
Let's get rid of that meat then.
Turn it into blood.
There we go, full health again.
The chainsaw somehow proves even better.
You know, like the fact that you can also do that with it.
It's just endless fun with the chainsaw.
Wait, what happened here?
Oh, a worm.
Chop it up.
Yes.
Oh, that's how we get worm blood easily, dude.
I was wondering why all the other times we didn't get any blood and sometimes we did.
Oh, it makes sense.
Look at all the blood.
Not that I needed...
Oh, I could have done this before I went in.
Well, I guess I explored it without vision.
Yeah, very neat.
You live, you learn.
Dude, I've learned so much today.
Every single time I get a run going here, I learn something new and incredible.
Whoops, didn't mean to destroy that.
Oh, I've been here before.
All right, let's go through.
We've got the money.
Let's go.
We do not heal.
We save that.
Aha.
See, now I'm sad I didn't keep the damn fireballs.
What did I say before?
What if we get a speed up?
By the way, I shouldn't have bought it instantly.
I'm an idiot.
I should have looked at the other things first.
Please tell me there's only shit here.
Okay, thank God.
Thank God.
What's that?
We take that.
Fire and brimstone?
I am not a feared.
In fact, I welcome it.
I welcome it with open arms.
Throw that away.
Hold on, is this even?
No, I don't want that.
Okay, what do we do?
Do we have a sick wand?
Oh, this is what I want to do.
I want to put speed on this one.
Cost three mana.
Oh, yeah.
Look at the distance on this now.
Lovely.
And you know what?
Because we go so fast with it.
Let me actually try to.
Use, where is it?
This one instead.
It's not if you have extra speed.
I can shoot this a long time.
That's lovely.
Okay, very cool.
Um, can we do anything digging wise?
Also, I said I would put this on one and they never did.
Hmm, let's see.
Digging, digging, digging.
Maybe that will dig.
I'm not honestly entirely certain on that, but we can use this.
On that.
Oh, wait, this is shuffle, so we need to do this.
Oh, but wait, it bounces off.
I don't like the way that does that.
But maybe I have to live with that.
Yeah.
I'm immune to fire and brimstone.
I'm immune to all this shit.
Oh, wait.
Everything gets blocked.
This is digging.
If it digs.
I don't know if it digs, but we'll have to see.
That is a potential digger.
These ones.
Yeah, maybe not.
What else should we make?
We could put light on something.
Okay, I wanted to put a light on this now, but...
Oh, wait, do we need to spread?
Yeah, we need to spread.
Much better.
Very nice.
Dude, flamethrower, we're not a fear of fire.
We are going all in on...
Am I also immune to that?
I may be.
Let's use it.
Let's use that instead.
That seems fun.
Now this one, should we do anything with it?
We could try to have some fun with that.
No, but you know what?
I may just keep these and then...
Because if I find another one, I want to replace it.
How about we get rid of heavy spreads?
No, actually keep that one.
Get rid of that one.
I really like that this one reduces recharge time.
But then again, I have a bunch of chainsaws, so fuck that.
We can...
We can fuck with that.
Yep.
And we're ready to go.
Cool.
It's easy base time.
I have come for your hits.
Wait a minute.
Friend-o-s.
Oh, not a friend-o.
Oh, kill them all.
In fact, I just realized I don't have any pheromone anyway.
And we have a bunch of blood.
Oh yeah, this is fine, this is fine, this is totally fine.
In fact, let me just drink all this warm blood.
Yeah, give us vision.
Vision of things not meant to be seen.
Wait, it actually helps me explore normally too.
Yo!
Why didn't I consider this?
Like it gives me vision of like...
What's to come around the corner?
That's dope.
Why did I not think about that?
I'm an idiot.
Of course it would do that.
See, another thing learned, another thing in the learning book.
Pick all this blood up, please.
There we go.
Sweet.
Oh, everything is trippy.
A little bit when you're on warm blood.
450 seconds of it.
I'm not a fear to fire.
Or explosions.
Dude, that actually means...
I was about to say it means I can withstand these that just exploded, but I can't because I'm not immune to frost damage.
I don't even know if that's a thing I can become immune to.
I have not even seen a perk like that.
Or maybe.
Electricity though, I'm not immune to.
Let's keep that in mind.
This one should be fine.
Yeah, I think it's fine.
I don't care about anything.
That was a friend though, but I don't care real.
Oh, grab the money.
Explode myself because it's fun.
That's a table.
Very sturdy construction there.
Hey guys.
Away from that one.
Heal up a bit.
Oh my god.
Blood!
Look at all the blood.
I feel like I have leveled up my vampirism skill.
After discovering first, the bottle method.
And second, the chainsaw method.
Those two combined makes me unstoppable.
I'm just saying.
That changed my life.
Come on.
Hello.
What's up my dude?
We've got a little shop here.
Horizontal barrier.
Accelerating shot.
Magic arrow with trigger.
Maybe.
Actually.
Oh, I don't even...
Wait, why can't I buy it?
Oh, I have no more room.
Throw this in the fucking water.
Throw...
When would you ever use this?
I feel like it sucks.
So does this.
Unless you combine that with a reduced spread, I guess.
But then you have a double spell.
Why not just use that, right?
Maybe you haven't found one.
Of course.
That makes sense.
Excuse me.
The fuck is that?
Hold the phone.
Can I get in there?
I can't dig with this.
My disappointment is immense and my day is ruined.
I forget the quote.
It's from the...
How do I get in there?
Can I chainsaw that at all?
Actually, yeah.
I can get in.
Hey!
Wait, can I?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's slow, but it works.
Yeah, I definitely can.
Yes, sir.
Just chill for a second here.
Why is my...
Oh, I get it.
That's how I...
Oh, man.
I was like, why is everything so weirdly colored?
I forgot I had this on.
That's...
Oh my...
Dude, I need to have worm blood on all the time.
There's all kinds of things.
Drain it!
Drain-o!
It's an American product.
I know about that one.
Yes!
An hourglass?
Blood?
Fill it with blood.
Fill it up all the way.
We need more blood.
Hold on.
I know for a fact that we have blood bags.
Also, why am I so...
Oh, I overate.
Isn't that just a little too close to home?
It's always overeating.
Look at all that blood!
Oh, man.
In fact, I could even...
It's annoying to go all the way around all the time.
It's fine.
You know what would be a great method to put blood in here?
If I had telekinetic kick, I could bring a corpse here and saw it up in here.
It's a little gruesome, but it works.
How do I get in, though?
Oh,
it's glass!
Oh!
Oh, my God!
But what was that up there?
It's an eye.
Well, well, well.
We struck gold.
In fact, let me take a look around, see if there's nothing else around me.
Dude.
This right...
Okay.
Wormy vision is actually insane.
We need to have that on all the time.
As much as we can, at least.
It is wildly good.
Give me that.
What is that one?
Ground to sand.
Oh, that's the one that only has eight charges to it.
Nah, I don't want that.
No thanks.
Oh!
Wait, we're close to the anvil, too!
It's anvil time, baby!
Oh, wait.
Let's grab some blood.
I want to murder that dude.
That's a friendo.
How do I get down there?
I guess I just dig it.
Sup?
What do we got there?
A bunch of rock spirits.
No thanks.
Oh, that's an electric.
Get rid of it.
Dude, this wand is fun!
It's amazing.
I love it so much!
And we make blood all the time.
This is the best.
It's the best.
Look at these fools.
They're having a party!
Well, so am I.
Oh, yeah!
Fuck all your drinks!
Kill it all!
Oh, it's lovely.
Amazing.
I'm unstoppable.
I can't be stopped.
Let's not get rid of that snow.
It actually contains the blood.
We love blood in this house.
Let's not get too overeager!
Goddamn, this wand is amazing.
Oh, yeah!
Oh, it's so good.
Dude, fire immunity is so freeing.
Octagonal bolt bundle.
Makes the projectile launch eight magical bolts.
If it moves slowly enough.
Hold on, let me try this, by the way.
Am I immune to that?
I may be.
It's hard to tell.
I think I may take this.
Just replace this wand, right?
Although this wand is kind of shit.
Yeah, we don't want it.
Dude, explosion and fire immunity is actually insane-o style.
I don't say it's insane-o style for anything.
So when I say it, you know it matters.
Can I...
I cannot get through there.
But is this enough?
It is not.
Even the strongest of the magic missiles does not have the power to penetrate steel.
Oh, yeah.
God, that's so satisfying.
After having been scared for so long, what is that?
Why is my potion filled with flammable gas?
Say what?
What the fuck is this?
Okay.
Oh, put blood in there, please.
That's what we all came to drink.
Fill it up.
Wow, we didn't even explode and set that shit on fire.
That's very unusual.
If I can get electric immunity, I'm set.
I mean, I know I'm asking for a lot here.
I already have the best of the best.
But you know, just a taste.
Just a bit more.
Some of that good stuff.
I'm sorry, friendo, but you don't get to live.
Look how it bounces off things.
This is a sick one.
I love it.
Totally shoot around corners with this bad boy.
In fact, hold on.
I see corpses.
You know what to do.
Yes.
You know, in the beginning, I thought the vampirism shit was really bad.
Because the healing was so slight and it didn't do anything.
Boy, was I wrong.
I wonder how many other things I'm wrong about, you know?
Did I just drink steel?
Have I become the man of steel?
I actually stunlocked the enemies so fast, they don't even shoot back.
I am cleansing this place.
This is way too much fun, guys.
It's like a... I don't even know, like a power fantasy.
Right now, this is just too good.
Oh, yeah.
We don't care about fire, we just get the blood and we heal up.
I do wish the screen wouldn't flicker when I get fired on, though.
Like, I'm immune to it, so don't make me nervous with the screen flickering, please.
Oh, man,
having fire mirrors in this place.
Does it get better than this?
I don't think so.
Now we make blood.
Wherever we can.
Dodge that one.
Full health.
I can't believe I haven't found any hearts in here, huh?
I never thought I had this much fun with this spell.
Oh, yes.
This is my dream.
Be careful here, it's getting a little dicey.
I'm getting a little too brazen.
Drink all of this.
Toy!
We got a wand up here.
I can't be stopped.
I am the master of the universe.
Come at me, brothers.
If you get hit, it's your own fault.
Holy shit!
Okay, let's be careful.
Let's calm down a bit.
It's getting a little too out of hand.
This is too much fun.
Get the blood, get the blood.
Drink, drink.
Did a guy die over here too?
I think so.
He had a wand!
A red glimmer with a swallow egg.
In fact, I'm going to take it.
Just because I want to fulfill that experiment I never got to experiment with last time.
But I need the other egg for that as well.
I want to test both.
Uh, drink blood.
Oh, there's so much blood here.
This is going to be a feast.
It's like bloods.
Beg on the menu, boys.
Cut it up.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
That's lovely, that.
That's lovely, governor.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, that's so good.
Drink.
Fill.
Go.
Kill.
Lots of dill.
Don't stay in the blue shit.
Stay in the red shit.
In fact, anything that's red in this game right now is my friend.
Anything that's blue is bad.
Blue, bad, red, good.
Blood, good.
Fire, good.
Explosion, mega nice.
Drink, drink, drink.
Oh, we're full on HP.
I don't even need to drink.
I don't know what I'm doing.
Wow.
Oh, yeah.
He sniped me.
That little asshole.
Fuck, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Get the blood.
Wait, what's that?
Oil.
Let's not drink that.
Let's get rid of oil.
In fact, I pour oil on myself.
Douse myself in oil.
And burn.
Cleanse the...
Purify.
I can't speak.
Let the flame purify my soul.
Is what I meant to say.
Get the blood.
Where are all the hordes?
Maybe there's been a...
Dude, someone put a little surprise for his roommate.
You see that?
Hey, gather up.
Who did this?
Who put that there?
That's bad manners.
We don't do that here.
Fill up the flask.
I
need more blood shit.
Ouch.
Oh, molten.
Doesn't matter.
I drink it.
Molten metal for breakfast.
Don't mind if I do.
What do we got over here?
In fact, I have one weakness in this game.
It's bullets.
My only weakness.
Come
on, fill up the flask, man.
Or just drink.
That's fine too.
That works.
It would almost make sense to make a once, purely with...
Chinso on it.
And no other spell, because this spell I have here is actually pushing around the bodies.
It's making it harder to saw it up, you know?
Oh yeah, look at that.
Lovely stuff.
Blood is overflowing.
Now, if I find a perk, or blood, blood, blood, I'm actually taking it.
Just for the fun.
It's gonna be the best if that happens.
Made my way through.
Oh, wait a minute.
I never went to the anvil.
I was too focused on the blood.
We gotta go anvil.
It's anvil time.
Doo doo doo doo doo.
Ah, yeah.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Come on.
Let me out.
Yeah.
Takes a bit of work to dig with this wand.
But you can make it work if you force it hard enough.
Oh, almost fell into a portal.
That was not my intention, no?
Shit, dead end.
What is that?
It's rotten meat?
Make blood!
And drink it.
Mm.
Very good.
I can get through here.
Easy peasy.
Show me the anvil.
What the fuck?
Someone left a little thing in there as well.
It's jiggling around.
It's the jiggler.
Oops, blue's bad, blue's bad, red is good.
Whoa!
What a shot!
That was amazing.
That guy just sniped that little bottle next to me.
Incredible performance.
I gotta applaud him for that.
What a snipe.
Wait a minute, that's a wand!
Exquisite me!
Now hold the phone.
You know what?
I doubt this is gonna work anyway with my theory, so I may just replace this for now.
I want these.
We can make something cool with that, I think.
Yes, sir.
It's not a plasma cutter, but it is what it is, you know?
It is what it is.
Blow it!
To smithereens.
God, I wanna teleport wand right now.
So bad.
This is, like, so slow for me.
I've gotten used to the Fast and Furious lifestyle.
Kill him!
Where's this anvil, huh?
Ah!
Look at all that blood.
We're gonna take it.
That is just lovely, isn't it?
That's lovely, isn't it?
Oh, yeah.
Fantastic.
Show me the goods.
Why is there electricity there?
What's happening?
Say what now?
Make blood.
There it is!
And we'll spot it.
Boink.
Random damage.
Huh.
Actually, that wand is not half bad.
I can dig it.
But can it dig?
See, that's another question.
I may just replace this wand right here.
I'm sorry, but this stuff right here does not entice me.
Even with that on.
Or does it?
Let me think.
That is a lot of mana and...
Hold on.
Actually, it has a very low mana charge speed, but with this on, it's actually not half bad.
Maybe I'll replace this.
I don't like this one.
It's also shuffled.
Fuck it.
Yeah, we want that for sure.
And then I'm going to experiment with the random damage.
We need to see what the hell is going on there.
All right, let's go.
I'm feeling it right now, man.
3k money as well.
Okay, none of these spells entice me at all.
However, I like that.
Thank you very much.
I shall be obtaining that and hopefully some more stuff in the future.
Unfortunately, I didn't get that early on, though.
So these spells are actually not digging at all for me.
But these are.
Hold on.
This costs 30 mana.
Add mana adds 30 mana, no?
Wait, why is it doing that?
Oh, wait, that drains mana quick.
What?
Oh, right.
Okay, so.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
If we do.
What if we do this?
Oh, that's funny.
Look at that.
It produces a chainsaw at the beginning of the one at the end of the wand and then at the end of the spell as well.
That's cool.
Oh, or only have it at the end.
Very nice.
That's actually really cool.
That's going to do some digging.
Random damage.
Let's test that, huh?
Wait, blood mist!
Wait, wait, wait.
What do you mean?
Oh, no way!
Wait.
Does that fill up my water bottle while standing on it?
Wow, it's a healing wand!
Dude.
Okay, that's awesome.
Hold on.
Let me try something.
Let's see this.
So this one has eight damage.
So if we just shoot that...
you know, eight, 16, 24, so on.
However, with this on, eight, 18.
88?!
Wait, is it ever lower?
Bro.
Dude, on average, that is insane.
It does say randomly increases or lowers.
But it never lowers.
It's always minimum eight.
No, am I crazy?
28, eight, eight, 48, 48, eight.
It doesn't go lower than eight.
Look.
Uh-oh, someone's coming.
Dude, we need to put this up here immediately.
Oh, we need to speed up, though.
Maybe we can live without the reduced spread, huh?
Oh, wait, let's see.
However, it does cost 15 mana.
That's the...
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What if we do this?
No, never mind.
I was about to put it down, but we don't have enough slots for that.
I don't need these here.
Oh, I've only had one more slot on this one.
That would be...
Ah, wait.
Wait, 15.
Dude, this is the wand.
What am I talking about?
This is it right here.
Right?
Hold on.
Oh, almost, almost.
More chainsaw.
Shit.
Oh, well.
We can fill a bottle with that, I guess.
Yes, sir!
And then...
Okay, okay, cool, cool.
We can maybe even do...
What about this one?
Okay, it drains mana quick.
That's the issue here.
The nice thing about this one is it doesn't drain mana as quick because it's so cheap.
Accelerating...
How much does that cost?
20 mana.
Remove bounce could be neat on this.
I don't...
I'm not sure...
No, I actually like the bounce.
I like the bounce.
I like to bounce it.
So, wait a minute.
There was one more thing I wanted to add here.
Oh!
Reduce spread!
Reduce spread.
Where did I...
There.
That costs only one mana.
That's sick.
Wait.
Eight.
Twenty-eight.
Wait, why does it not show damage for some of the shots?
What?
Hold on.
There's something I'm not getting here.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I have an idea.
Can we...
Can we double-dip on this one?
Oh.
Oh, no, no, no.
That's gonna affect...
Unless...
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
It's double-dipping time, baby.
What if we do this?
No, wait, that's not gonna work.
No.
Shit.
I thought we could double-dip on it.
I mean, that's solid.
That's really good.
Let me try it without that.
Oh, yeah, look, it's way worse.
Damn, what a...
That's insanity.
That's actually really good.
That is really nice.
What if we add an extra chainsaw?
What then?
Is that just me or is it slower?
Or maybe it does nothing.
Oh, that definitely...
We need one more there.
What if we change it up like that?
Does that make a difference?
Wait, are we double-dipping on the speed up?
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Hold on.
Let me see how far it goes.
Oh, that goes really far.
Look!
The double-dip!
The double-dippy-do!
It's deepening!
That's insanity.
Very nice.
Okay, by the way, double-dippy-do is a double IPA beer I really like.
It's called double-dippy-do, I shit your nut.
Okay, what do we do with all these drills here, though?
Let's put them here, I guess.
And then we put that there.
I love this.
Actually, hold on.
Why don't I just do this?
What am I talking about?
This is a storage wand right now.
We are storaging.
No, it's a storage slash shoot these spells wand.
Give some light on that as well.
And sure, why not some drill?
Except that could be a little dangerous.
We don't need all these drills.
No, no, we need one drill.
That's fine.
This is good.
This is real good.
There we go.
And then we need...
Hold on, let's see the damage.
Not a noticeable increase there.
Whoops.
Actually, hold on.
Why is that super low suddenly?
I mean, I guess it is sort of RNG.
Yeah, I like this more.
You go much less fast.
Much slower.
Now this wand is actually still a decent wand.
What if we were to just chainsaw it?
This is our meat cutter.
We be cutting meats.
Can we improve the meat cutting?
Add some light to it.
We don't want to cut meat in the dark.
That's important.
I think that's good, man.
We could add homing or something.
No, this is fine.
Okay.
Healing, we don't need.
Everything is fine.
Let's go.
Let's take a look at how this works.
Whoa.
So far, so good.
In fact, actually, hold on.
I need to stop here.
It's getting way too late.
This game has a way of stealing your time out of your hands.
Just immediately.
In fact, I may have to go immediately.
It's a little too late here.
I have some meetings tomorrow.
Wait a minute.
I can chat for a couple of minutes.
What's up, peoples?
Huh?
What do you think about that?
Hopefully, you weren't too disappointed with my death in that other run.
Huh?
I feel like we paid...
That was the prize for a lot of good information and knowledge we gained.
And discovery is made.
You know?
But maybe I'm just a little copiumed up.
The moment I saw your dick towards electricity, I knew it was over.
No!
Wait, you saw it coming too.
That means I could have seen it coming if I paid attention.
That makes me feel good, actually.
Creamy mommy.
That's an awesome emote.
Where the hell did you find that?
That's amazing.
And very bloody.
Knowledge through pain, wisdom through sacrifice.
And I like that.
Did you say that?
If offered, which one of these will you choose?
Electric immunity, fire immunity, vampirism.
Depends when I discover it in the run.
If it's very early, I would say vampirism.
Or actually, yeah.
Honestly, I would say vampirism over everything there.
Followed by fire immunity.
Simply because of what I just experienced.
If it wasn't for this last run up until now, I would have said electric.
But I just discovered how fucking good fire immunity actually is.
You don't think about it, but the freedom that it gives you is unmatched.
Doing great, I was surprised that your hours are low, but you're knowledgeable.
I've been doing a lot of suffering though to get that knowledge, legit hacks.
But thank you.
Thank you for saying that.
I appreciate it.
In fact, the game is lying because I have more deaths than it says in game.
I should have 75 or something deaths now, even though the game says 73.
It's weird.
Ghost with sawblades was awesome.
It was, it was.
That one caught me off guard, man.
Right after I picked up some sawblades myself.
Holy shit, man.
The emotes you guys have of the Ookie and what is that?
Someone petting?
Some kind of thing.
And the friendo.
How are you doing that?
Is that?
How are you doing those emotes?
I want to do those emotes.
The hemistance is not really what I envisioned.
I managed to edit the gif I was thinking of.
But it wasn't just reverse because I put that put it in reverse and I also switched direction on it horizontally.
You can click on them and see which channel is from.
Oh.
Oh, let's suffer together.
We raided that guy once.
I remember this.
Yo, that's awesome.
Very cool.
Yo, that's neat.
Yeah, abandoned runs don't count as deaths.
Oh, is that real?
Okay, wait, did I have abandoned runs?
Oh, I guess the one that bugged out and I had to restart.
No, wait, I killed myself in that.
No, I didn't.
I did restart, didn't I?
Oh, light my violet.
Thank you so much for rating, but I actually I'm ending it right now.
We just finished a five hour stream.
What's up, everyone?
I had a crazy run today and last time that unfortunately ended in a very unfortunate way, as always.
But now I'm on a new run, a new and improved run and it's insane and I can't wait to continue it next time.
Yeah, I'm ending it right now, but thank you very much anyway.
In fact, I'm gonna raid someone else now.
So the raiders from light my violet, you can stay and I'm streaming Neuter right now.
Same category.
Oh, you're streaming.
I'm gonna send everyone back to you, unless you're stopping.
I guess you only raid when you stop a stream.
Someone German is playing it.
Oh, someone is streaming Neuter with the title, Newbie Neuter stream sent help.
Wrote to one win.
We gotta send that guy some love.
We gotta raid that guy.
I'm gonna start a raid here.
I wish this guy all the luck to get his first win.
Thank you so much for watching everybody and subscribing and thank you for the raid, light my violet.
I appreciate it.
This has been a blast as always.
I'll see you guys around, okay?
Have a good night.
Goodbye.